[
  {
    "type": "visitors-list",
    "dates": [
      {
        "date": "2017-01-12,2017-01-18",
        "items": [
          { "time":"1484782762", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 3:39pm", "time_total":"59", "ip_address":"86.23.42.255", "uid":"1010385413", "session_id":"454618276", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484782762", "session_id":"454618276"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/misys/summit/superior-networking-inspirational-thought-leadership", "web_browser":"Unknown mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"https://t.co/pP9pFLvMhM", "referrer_domain":"t.co", "referrer_type":"social media", "geolocation":"Harrow, The United Kingdom", "country_code":"gb", "latitude":"51.5667", "longitude":"-0.3333", "hostname":"virginm.net", "organization":"Virgin Media", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454618276"},
          { "time":"1484780642", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 3:04pm", "time_total":"360", "ip_address":"97.32.139.177", "uid":"1283799877", "session_id":"454578589", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484780642", "session_id":"454578589"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 43.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x480", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454578589"},
          { "time":"1484780381", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 2:59pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"73.14.153.44", "uid":"1198973829", "session_id":"454573314", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484780381", "session_id":"454573314"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Arvada, Colorado, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.8288", "longitude":"-105.0607", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454573314"},
          { "time":"1484774193", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 1:16pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"68.98.131.233", "uid":"1066819425", "session_id":"454436938", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484774193", "session_id":"454436938"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Falls Church, Virginia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.8601", "longitude":"-77.1531", "hostname":"cox.net", "organization":"Cox Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454436938"},
          { "time":"1484773327", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 1:02pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.143.88.69", "uid":"963921012", "session_id":"454416282", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484773327", "session_id":"454416282"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Pompano Beach, Florida, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"26.2720", "longitude":"-80.2580", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454416282"},
          { "time":"1484773308", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 1:01pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.199.115", "uid":"1829546690", "session_id":"454415846", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484773308", "session_id":"454415846"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"30.4507", "longitude":"-91.1546", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454415846"},
          { "time":"1484772471", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 12:47pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"197.156.95.214", "uid":"192928723", "session_id":"454396677", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484772471", "session_id":"454396677"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Ethiopia", "country_code":"et", "latitude":"8.0000", "longitude":"38.0000", "organization":"Ethiopian Telecommunication Corporation", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454396677"},
          { "time":"1484772425", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 12:47pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"75.156.152.228", "uid":"1074103578", "session_id":"454395576", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484772425", "session_id":"454395576"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Calgary, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"51.1111", "longitude":"-114.0477", "hostname":"telus.net", "organization":"Telus Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454395576"},
          { "time":"1484772089", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 12:41pm", "time_total":"30", "ip_address":"177.226.8.111", "uid":"3411135598", "session_id":"454387092", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484772089", "session_id":"454387092"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"Spanish", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Le√≥n, Mexico", "country_code":"mx", "latitude":"21.1167", "longitude":"-101.6667", "hostname":"megared.net.mx", "organization":"Mega Cable, S.a. De C.v.", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454387092"},
          { "time":"1484771608", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 12:33pm", "time_total":"30", "ip_address":"174.255.129.140", "uid":"1975016568", "session_id":"454375954", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484771608", "session_id":"454375954"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x534", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454375954"},
          { "time":"1484771262", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 12:27pm", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"172.56.19.10", "uid":"1613573130", "session_id":"454368186", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484769039", "session_id":"454317387"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"The Bronx, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8690", "longitude":"-73.9023", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454368186"},
          { "time":"1484770915", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 12:21pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"172.58.68.133", "uid":"1081027442", "session_id":"454360509", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484770915", "session_id":"454360509"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.5874", "longitude":"-97.5218", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454360509"},
          { "time":"1484770795", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 12:19pm", "time_total":"150", "ip_address":"172.56.36.157", "uid":"3911187941", "session_id":"454357795", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484770795", "session_id":"454357795"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Elizabeth, New Jersey, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6769", "longitude":"-74.2155", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454357795"},
          { "time":"1484770617", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 12:16pm", "time_total":"37", "ip_address":"197.148.73.1", "uid":"404499936", "session_id":"454353781", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484770617", "session_id":"454353781"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 40.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x534", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Banjul, The Gambia", "country_code":"gm", "latitude":"13.4531", "longitude":"-16.5775", "organization":"Africell-gm", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454353781"},
          { "time":"1484770524", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 12:15pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"50.191.241.71", "uid":"743081858", "session_id":"454351626", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484770524", "session_id":"454351626"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.0192", "longitude":"-75.0940", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454351626"},
          { "time":"1484770056", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 12:07pm", "time_total":"481", "ip_address":"172.58.14.236", "uid":"2964618305", "session_id":"454341073", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484770056", "session_id":"454341073"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"Spanish", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.4484", "longitude":"-112.0740", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454341073"},
          { "time":"1484769936", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 12:05pm", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"107.50.154.35", "uid":"2329448469", "session_id":"454338468", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484769936", "session_id":"454338468"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Howell, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.6990", "longitude":"-83.8860", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454338468"},
          { "time":"1484769935", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 12:05pm", "time_total":"137", "ip_address":"208.54.85.170", "uid":"2087557110", "session_id":"454338448", "actions":"3", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484769935", "session_id":"454338448"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Firefox 50.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"28.0222", "longitude":"-81.7329", "hostname":"tmodns.net", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454338448"},
          { "time":"1484769859", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 12:04pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"71.82.46.158", "uid":"3236462411", "session_id":"454336627", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484769859", "session_id":"454336627"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x534", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Belton, South Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.4877", "longitude":"-82.4953", "hostname":"charter.com", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454336627"},
          { "time":"1484769731", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 12:02pm", "time_total":"239", "ip_address":"212.34.12.151", "uid":"3316343462", "session_id":"454333628", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484769731", "session_id":"454333628"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"Arabic", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Amman, Jordan", "country_code":"jo", "latitude":"31.9500", "longitude":"35.9333", "organization":"Jordan Telecommunications Company", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454333628"},
          { "time":"1484769679", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 12:01pm", "time_total":"30", "ip_address":"185.136.148.59", "uid":"2438113323", "session_id":"454332363", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484769679", "session_id":"454332363"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"600x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"Arabic", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Iraq", "country_code":"iq", "latitude":"33.0000", "longitude":"44.0000", "organization":"Kurdistan Net Company For Computer And Internet Lt", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454332363"},
          { "time":"1484769592", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:59am", "time_total":"61", "ip_address":"107.77.203.203", "uid":"4113371952", "session_id":"454330219", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484769592", "session_id":"454330219"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 28.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"480x854", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chadds Ford, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.8554", "longitude":"-75.6342", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454330219"},
          { "time":"1484769440", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:57am", "time_total":"130", "ip_address":"71.84.131.185", "uid":"4015092499", "session_id":"454326720", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484769440", "session_id":"454326720"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Toledo, Oregon, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"44.6012", "longitude":"-123.8920", "hostname":"charter.com", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454326720"},
          { "time":"1484769292", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:54am", "time_total":"240", "ip_address":"64.121.55.85", "uid":"2191870802", "session_id":"454323198", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484769292", "session_id":"454323198"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"601x962", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Allentown, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6152", "longitude":"-75.5437", "hostname":"rcn.com", "organization":"Rcn", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454323198"},
          { "time":"1484769197", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:53am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"168.169.226.60", "uid":"2809164197", "session_id":"454320983", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484769197", "session_id":"454320983"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Hamburg, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.7091", "longitude":"-78.8301", "hostname":"wnyric.org", "organization":"Erie 1 Boces", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454320983"},
          { "time":"1484769173", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:52am", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"172.58.153.242", "uid":"119368980", "session_id":"454320383", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484769173", "session_id":"454320383"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Norcross, Georgia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.9443", "longitude":"-84.2124", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454320383"},
          { "time":"1484769135", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:52am", "time_total":"1167", "ip_address":"216.10.232.20", "uid":"2839882742", "session_id":"454319451", "actions":"6", "total_visits":"16", "first_visit": {"time":"1480450383", "session_id":"380216613"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/?product=summit", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Windows 10", "screen_resolution":"1366x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com/", "referrer_domain":"2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Harrow, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"42.0363", "longitude":"-82.9182", "organization":"G1 Hispeed", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454319451"},
          { "time":"1484769053", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:50am", "time_total":"53", "ip_address":"47.208.63.245", "uid":"587375846", "session_id":"454317740", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484769053", "session_id":"454317740"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x534", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Eureka, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8021", "longitude":"-124.1637", "hostname":"suddenlink.net", "organization":"Suddenlink Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454317740"},
          { "time":"1484769039", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:50am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"172.56.19.10", "uid":"1613573130", "session_id":"454317387", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484769039", "session_id":"454317387"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"The Bronx, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8690", "longitude":"-73.9023", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454317387"},
          { "time":"1484768959", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:49am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"74.105.65.246", "uid":"739148351", "session_id":"454315497", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484768959", "session_id":"454315497"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Long Branch, New Jersey, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.2944", "longitude":"-73.9932", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Fios", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454315497"},
          { "time":"1484768942", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:49am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"206.82.19.254", "uid":"1100723854", "session_id":"454315200", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484768942", "session_id":"454315200"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Elizabethtown, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.1680", "longitude":"-76.6093", "hostname":"etownschools.org", "organization":"Lancaster Lebanon Intermediate Unit 13", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454315200"},
          { "time":"1484768916", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:48am", "time_total":"35", "ip_address":"174.192.13.195", "uid":"3167352983", "session_id":"454314560", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484768916", "session_id":"454314560"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Boston, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.3660", "longitude":"-71.1230", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454314560"},
          { "time":"1484768819", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:46am", "time_total":"360", "ip_address":"172.58.201.130", "uid":"271070259", "session_id":"454312523", "actions":"4", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484768819", "session_id":"454312523"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Cleveland, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.4995", "longitude":"-81.6954", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454312523"},
          { "time":"1484768798", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:46am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.113.175.168", "uid":"2412637046", "session_id":"454311997", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484768798", "session_id":"454311997"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Toronto, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"43.7135", "longitude":"-79.3887", "hostname":"rogers.com", "organization":"Rogers Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454311997"},
          { "time":"1484768756", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:45am", "time_total":"357", "ip_address":"198.14.231.41", "uid":"3095834726", "session_id":"454310967", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484768756", "session_id":"454310967"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Hemphill, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"31.3281", "longitude":"-93.8082", "organization":"Windstream Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454310967"},
          { "time":"1484768733", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:45am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"174.199.27.254", "uid":"2916858857", "session_id":"454310472", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484768733", "session_id":"454310472"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Manchester, Connecticut, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.7770", "longitude":"-72.5236", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454310472"},
          { "time":"1484768560", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:42am", "time_total":"365", "ip_address":"174.255.129.73", "uid":"2403601554", "session_id":"454306399", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484768560", "session_id":"454306399"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454306399"},
          { "time":"1484768521", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:42am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"68.45.123.28", "uid":"698053625", "session_id":"454305454", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484768521", "session_id":"454305454"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Berne, Indiana, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6588", "longitude":"-84.9350", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454305454"},
          { "time":"1484768406", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:40am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"76.18.21.12", "uid":"2879873590", "session_id":"454302710", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484768406", "session_id":"454302710"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Fort Lauderdale, Florida, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"26.1136", "longitude":"-80.4153", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454302710"},
          { "time":"1484767963", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:32am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.107.138.93", "uid":"3518249360", "session_id":"454292001", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484767963", "session_id":"454292001"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Myrtle Beach, South Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.6985", "longitude":"-78.9032", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454292001"},
          { "time":"1484767852", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:30am", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"172.58.168.160", "uid":"3829018242", "session_id":"454289349", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484767852", "session_id":"454289349"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Auburndale, Florida, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"28.0795", "longitude":"-81.8037", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454289349"},
          { "time":"1484767445", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:24am", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"47.20.245.131", "uid":"2032923062", "session_id":"454279609", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484767445", "session_id":"454279609"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"534x320", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Brooklyn, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6201", "longitude":"-73.9868", "hostname":"optonline.net", "organization":"Optimum Online", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454279609"},
          { "time":"1484767322", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:22am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.228.139.105", "uid":"3341566780", "session_id":"454276712", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484767322", "session_id":"454276712"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454276712"},
          { "time":"1484766615", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 11:10am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"12.28.158.22", "uid":"2645497655", "session_id":"454259465", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484766615", "session_id":"454259465"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Amarillo, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.1145", "longitude":"-101.7712", "organization":"Canyon Isd", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454259465"},
          { "time":"1484765875", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 10:57am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"50.157.42.98", "uid":"3589587943", "session_id":"454242095", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484765875", "session_id":"454242095"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Southaven, Mississippi, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.9489", "longitude":"-89.9665", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454242095"},
          { "time":"1484765745", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 10:55am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"162.199.60.49", "uid":"3712443461", "session_id":"454239138", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484765745", "session_id":"454239138"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Dallas, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.8441", "longitude":"-96.8326", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454239138"},
          { "time":"1484760297", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 9:24am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"47.20.245.131", "uid":"3506477015", "session_id":"454107439", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484760297", "session_id":"454107439"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 34.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"490x320", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Brooklyn, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6201", "longitude":"-73.9868", "hostname":"optonline.net", "organization":"Optimum Online", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454107439"},
          { "time":"1484760073", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 9:21am", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"216.10.232.20", "uid":"2839882742", "session_id":"454101747", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"16", "first_visit": {"time":"1480450383", "session_id":"380216613"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/elastic/summit/priceless-guidance-for-building-our-program", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Windows 10", "screen_resolution":"1366x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com/", "referrer_domain":"2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Harrow, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"42.0363", "longitude":"-82.9182", "organization":"G1 Hispeed", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454101747"},
          { "time":"1484758433", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 8:53am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.213.157", "uid":"379021325", "session_id":"454059196", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"6", "first_visit": {"time":"1481897128", "session_id":"403325617"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://tpc.googlesyndication.com/", "referrer_domain":"tpc.googlesyndication.com", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0544", "longitude":"-118.2440", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454059196"},
          { "time":"1484757908", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 8:45am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.212.183", "uid":"1051371272", "session_id":"454045332", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484757908", "session_id":"454045332"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"414x736", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"https://securepubads.g.doubleclick.net/gampad/ads", "referrer_domain":"securepubads.g.doubleclick.net", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0544", "longitude":"-118.2440", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454045332"},
          { "time":"1484757375", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 8:36am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"24.147.171.19", "uid":"2330148344", "session_id":"454030962", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484757375", "session_id":"454030962"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Windows 7", "screen_resolution":"1600x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://tpc.googlesyndication.com/", "referrer_domain":"tpc.googlesyndication.com", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Boston, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.3496", "longitude":"-71.0746", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=454030962"},
          { "time":"1484750935", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 6:48am", "time_total":"243", "ip_address":"128.210.107.76", "uid":"4195091209", "session_id":"453864758", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484750935", "session_id":"453864758"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"West Lafayette, Indiana, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.4259", "longitude":"-86.9081", "organization":"Purdue University", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453864758"},
          { "time":"1484749758", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 6:29am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"216.209.120.53", "uid":"3941721769", "session_id":"453834763", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484749758", "session_id":"453834763"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Saint Fintan's, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"48.2000", "longitude":"-58.8667", "hostname":"bell.ca", "organization":"Bell Canada", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453834763"},
          { "time":"1484745650", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 5:20am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"98.5.205.245", "uid":"1077230262", "session_id":"453736739", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484529141", "session_id":"449757207"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Buffalo, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.8864", "longitude":"-78.8784", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453736739"},
          { "time":"1484740845", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 4am", "time_total":"243", "ip_address":"208.54.32.197", "uid":"2843160335", "session_id":"453631993", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484058769", "session_id":"439996276"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x480", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"tmodns.net", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453631993"},
          { "time":"1484739651", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 3:40am", "time_total":"538", "ip_address":"91.187.98.121", "uid":"4053066141", "session_id":"453609745", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"14", "first_visit": {"time":"1484151392", "session_id":"442121009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Albania", "country_code":"al", "latitude":"41.0000", "longitude":"20.0000", "organization":"Ipko Telecommunications Llc", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453609745"},
          { "time":"1484732942", "time_pretty":"Wed Jan 18 2017, 1:49am", "time_total":"125", "ip_address":"117.203.62.39", "uid":"380808342", "session_id":"453491455", "actions":"4", "total_visits":"8", "first_visit": {"time":"1481898836", "session_id":"403356867"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"600x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Visakhapatnam, India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"17.7000", "longitude":"83.3000", "organization":"Bsnl", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453491455"},
          { "time":"1484715329", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 8:55pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.211.138.21", "uid":"401403038", "session_id":"453263228", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484665266", "session_id":"452230717"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Los Angeles, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0438", "longitude":"-118.2512", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453263228"},
          { "time":"1484713526", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 8:25pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.205.48", "uid":"3503541312", "session_id":"453241003", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484538292", "session_id":"449897210"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.9597", "longitude":"-75.1968", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453241003"},
          { "time":"1484708217", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 6:56pm", "time_total":"82", "ip_address":"108.207.25.118", "uid":"3007999881", "session_id":"453170195", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484708217", "session_id":"453170195"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Camden, South Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.3177", "longitude":"-80.5771", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453170195"},
          { "time":"1484708034", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 6:53pm", "time_total":"352", "ip_address":"70.211.138.21", "uid":"401403038", "session_id":"453167609", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484665266", "session_id":"452230717"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Los Angeles, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0438", "longitude":"-118.2512", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453167609"},
          { "time":"1484707437", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 6:43pm", "time_total":"1386", "ip_address":"66.214.177.100", "uid":"829334053", "session_id":"453158955", "actions":"3", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484622188", "session_id":"451522009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"California City, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.1509", "longitude":"-117.9215", "hostname":"charter.com", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453158955"},
          { "time":"1484707324", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 6:42pm", "time_total":"30", "ip_address":"122.44.229.3", "uid":"2477007696", "session_id":"453157383", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484707324", "session_id":"453157383"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"Korean", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Seoul, Republic Of Korea", "country_code":"kr", "latitude":"37.5985", "longitude":"126.9783", "organization":"Powercomm", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453157383"},
          { "time":"1484707226", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 6:40pm", "time_total":"191", "ip_address":"73.208.168.2", "uid":"493494310", "session_id":"453155981", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484707226", "session_id":"453155981"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.7403", "longitude":"-87.6540", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453155981"},
          { "time":"1484707203", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 6:40pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"104.236.195.238", "uid":"87122412", "session_id":"453155679", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484707203", "session_id":"453155679"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/", "web_browser":"Firefox 28.0", "operating_system":"Windows 7", "screen_resolution":"1024x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7421", "longitude":"-74.0018", "organization":"Digital Ocean", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453155679"},
          { "time":"1484706521", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 6:28pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"98.198.5.15", "uid":"1463777701", "session_id":"453145669", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484706521", "session_id":"453145669"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Sugar Land, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"29.5557", "longitude":"-95.6335", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453145669"},
          { "time":"1484706143", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 6:22pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"162.221.154.11", "uid":"4108869778", "session_id":"453139971", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484706143", "session_id":"453139971"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Firefox 50.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1440x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://tpc.googlesyndication.com/", "referrer_domain":"tpc.googlesyndication.com", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Raleigh, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.8181", "longitude":"-78.5636", "organization":"Citrix", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453139971"},
          { "time":"1484706113", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 6:21pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"184.75.217.31", "uid":"953439037", "session_id":"453139492", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484706113", "session_id":"453139492"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 4.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"1366x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Toronto, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"43.6667", "longitude":"-79.4167", "hostname":"amanah.com", "organization":"Amanah Tech", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453139492"},
          { "time":"1484706049", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 6:20pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"73.132.1.20", "uid":"950897728", "session_id":"453138440", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484706049", "session_id":"453138440"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 8.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Alexandria, Virginia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.8337", "longitude":"-77.1204", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453138440"},
          { "time":"1484704491", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 5:54pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"98.198.5.15", "uid":"3741755857", "session_id":"453114228", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484704491", "session_id":"453114228"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Sugar Land, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"29.5557", "longitude":"-95.6335", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453114228"},
          { "time":"1484704055", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 5:47pm", "time_total":"602", "ip_address":"73.93.141.73", "uid":"1323113063", "session_id":"453107330", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484704055", "session_id":"453107330"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1440x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"https://varmour.com/product/architecture", "referrer_domain":"varmour.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"San Francisco, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7772", "longitude":"-122.4931", "organization":"Xfinity Wifi", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453107330"},
          { "time":"1484703445", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 5:37pm", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"74.47.104.200", "uid":"2932647363", "session_id":"453097407", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484703445", "session_id":"453097407"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Bullhead City, Arizona, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.0900", "longitude":"-114.5736", "hostname":"frontiernet.net", "organization":"Frontier Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453097407"},
          { "time":"1484703007", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 5:30pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"68.45.213.71", "uid":"3248659068", "session_id":"453090293", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484674897", "session_id":"452478627"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Fort Wayne, Indiana, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.0483", "longitude":"-85.0801", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453090293"},
          { "time":"1484702449", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 5:20pm", "time_total":"601", "ip_address":"70.198.45.41", "uid":"4071095516", "session_id":"453081372", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484702449", "session_id":"453081372"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Omaha, Nebraska, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.2563", "longitude":"-95.9404", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453081372"},
          { "time":"1484701771", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 5:09pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"108.228.158.186", "uid":"1129052282", "session_id":"453070209", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484701771", "session_id":"453070209"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Cleveland, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.5651", "longitude":"-81.5646", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453070209"},
          { "time":"1484700815", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 4:53pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"43.246.101.54", "uid":"380808342", "session_id":"453054653", "actions":"4", "total_visits":"8", "first_visit": {"time":"1481898836", "session_id":"403356867"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"600x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Visakhapatnam, India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"17.7000", "longitude":"83.3000", "organization":"Srinivasa Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453054653"},
          { "time":"1484700656", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 4:50pm", "time_total":"601", "ip_address":"162.221.154.11", "uid":"2785411658", "session_id":"453051915", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1482370563", "session_id":"409328067"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1440x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://quizone.co/q/4", "referrer_domain":"quizone.co", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Raleigh, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.8181", "longitude":"-78.5636", "organization":"Citrix", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=453051915"},
          { "time":"1484696831", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 3:47pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"129.63.209.78", "uid":"2341378851", "session_id":"452985616", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484617880", "session_id":"451457477"}, "landing_page":"https://trunity.customerstories.net/life-on-this-rock/life-on-this-rock-shea/introduction-to-biology-for-students-majoring-in-other-fields", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 50.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://trunity.com/", "referrer_domain":"trunity.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Lowell, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.6523", "longitude":"-71.3506", "organization":"University Of Massachusetts - Lowell", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452985616"},
          { "time":"1484696042", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 3:34pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"32.211.2.25", "uid":"1761156833", "session_id":"452971169", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484671754", "session_id":"452399531"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Meriden, Connecticut, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.5372", "longitude":"-72.7801", "organization":"Frontier Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452971169"},
          { "time":"1484693754", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 2:55pm", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"32.211.2.25", "uid":"1761156833", "session_id":"452927448", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484671754", "session_id":"452399531"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Meriden, Connecticut, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.5372", "longitude":"-72.7801", "organization":"Frontier Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452927448"},
          { "time":"1484693622", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 2:53pm", "time_total":"32", "ip_address":"12.17.168.202", "uid":"4226252213", "session_id":"452924907", "actions":"4", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484691402", "session_id":"452878874"}, "landing_page":"http://customerstories.net/", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1920x1080", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "geolocation":"San Francisco, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.8033", "longitude":"-122.4108", "organization":"At&t Services", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452924907"},
          { "time":"1484693509", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 2:51pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"68.0.204.63", "uid":"3235307137", "session_id":"452922537", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484693509", "session_id":"452922537"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"East Greenwich, Rhode Island, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.6434", "longitude":"-71.4783", "hostname":"cox.net", "organization":"Cox Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452922537"},
          { "time":"1484693037", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 2:43pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"66.87.120.218", "uid":"3306710513", "session_id":"452913189", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484663091", "session_id":"452176623"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.7787", "longitude":"-96.8217", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452913189"},
          { "time":"1484692333", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 2:32pm", "time_total":"61", "ip_address":"108.66.139.129", "uid":"741002392", "session_id":"452898679", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484672885", "session_id":"452428367"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"601x962", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"West Columbia, South Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.9900", "longitude":"-81.1016", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452898679"},
          { "time":"1484691793", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 2:23pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"172.56.36.173", "uid":"2947363535", "session_id":"452887103", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484691793", "session_id":"452887103"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Elizabeth, New Jersey, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6769", "longitude":"-74.2155", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452887103"},
          { "time":"1484691402", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 2:16pm", "time_total":"601", "ip_address":"12.17.168.202", "uid":"4226252213", "session_id":"452878874", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484691402", "session_id":"452878874"}, "landing_page":"http://customerstories.net/", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1920x1080", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "geolocation":"San Francisco, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.8033", "longitude":"-122.4108", "organization":"At&t Services", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452878874"},
          { "time":"1484690916", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 2:08pm", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"198.85.220.8", "uid":"2733578441", "session_id":"452868550", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484672090", "session_id":"452408497"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Greenville, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.6876", "longitude":"-77.1661", "organization":"City Of Greenville, Nc", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452868550"},
          { "time":"1484690388", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 1:59pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"4.35.234.196", "uid":"816532860", "session_id":"452857106", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484690388", "session_id":"452857106"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 4.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"240x320", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://googleads.g.doubleclick.net/", "referrer_domain":"googleads.g.doubleclick.net", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Fairfax, Virginia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.8357", "longitude":"-77.3375", "hostname":"level3.net", "organization":"Level 3 Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452857106"},
          { "time":"1484689594", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 1:46pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"32.211.2.25", "uid":"1761156833", "session_id":"452839337", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484671754", "session_id":"452399531"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Meriden, Connecticut, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.5372", "longitude":"-72.7801", "organization":"Frontier Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452839337"},
          { "time":"1484687462", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 1:11pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"66.102.6.1", "uid":"2718813183", "session_id":"452789805", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484687462", "session_id":"452789805"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/vocera/summit/value-received-broadening-customer-advocacy-experience", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Windows 7", "screen_resolution":"1366x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://google.co.uk/search?q=%5Bsecure+search%5D", "referrer_domain":"google.co.uk", "referrer_search":"[secure search]", "referrer_type":"search", "geolocation":"Mountain View, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.4192", "longitude":"-122.0574", "hostname":"google.com", "organization":"Google", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452789805"},
          { "time":"1484686337", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 12:52pm", "time_total":"336", "ip_address":"99.104.114.193", "uid":"2013357037", "session_id":"452762825", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484686337", "session_id":"452762825"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Rialto, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.1064", "longitude":"-117.3703", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452762825"},
          { "time":"1484684413", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 12:20pm", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"108.162.52.218", "uid":"2954344293", "session_id":"452716724", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484684413", "session_id":"452716724"}, "landing_page":"https://trunity.customerstories.net/integrating-concepts-in-biology/integrating-concepts-in-biology-campell-heyer-paradise/integrating-concepts-in-biology", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1440x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://trunity.com/", "referrer_domain":"trunity.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Stamford, Connecticut, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.0610", "longitude":"-73.5429", "hostname":"optonline.net", "organization":"Optimum Online", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452716724"},
          { "time":"1484681604", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 11:33am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.89.171.187", "uid":"3607231713", "session_id":"452647131", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484681604", "session_id":"452647131"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"800x1280", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Quinte West, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"44.1834", "longitude":"-77.5662", "hostname":"bell.ca", "organization":"Bell Canada", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452647131"},
          { "time":"1484681499", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 11:31am", "time_total":"245", "ip_address":"107.77.233.96", "uid":"231494649", "session_id":"452644529", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484681499", "session_id":"452644529"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8596", "longitude":"-73.9314", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452644529"},
          { "time":"1484681233", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 11:27am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"109.147.64.82", "uid":"1915114767", "session_id":"452637761", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484681233", "session_id":"452637761"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/vocera/summit/value-received-broadening-customer-advocacy-experience", "web_browser":"Unknown mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://lnkd.in/", "referrer_domain":"lnkd.in", "referrer_type":"social media", "geolocation":"Reading, The United Kingdom", "country_code":"gb", "latitude":"51.4712", "longitude":"-0.9421", "hostname":"btcentralplus.com", "organization":"Bt", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452637761"},
          { "time":"1484681172", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 11:26am", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"129.63.253.105", "uid":"2341378851", "session_id":"452636309", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484617880", "session_id":"451457477"}, "landing_page":"https://trunity.customerstories.net/life-on-this-rock/life-on-this-rock-shea/introduction-to-biology-for-students-majoring-in-other-fields", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 50.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://trunity.com/", "referrer_domain":"trunity.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Lowell, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.6523", "longitude":"-71.3506", "organization":"University Of Massachusetts - Lowell", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452636309"},
          { "time":"1484679844", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 11:04am", "time_total":"107", "ip_address":"74.77.192.166", "uid":"3385865033", "session_id":"452603478", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484679844", "session_id":"452603478"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Buffalo, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.8356", "longitude":"-78.7484", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452603478"},
          { "time":"1484679815", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 11:03am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"173.184.224.155", "uid":"792975604", "session_id":"452602743", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484679815", "session_id":"452602743"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Meadville, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.6465", "longitude":"-80.1733", "hostname":"windstream.net", "organization":"Windstream Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452602743"},
          { "time":"1484678670", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 10:44am", "time_total":"121", "ip_address":"174.194.137.30", "uid":"2733578441", "session_id":"452573820", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484672090", "session_id":"452408497"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Fayetteville, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.0570", "longitude":"-79.0147", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452573820"},
          { "time":"1484677803", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 10:30am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"24.31.185.223", "uid":"2781848127", "session_id":"452552429", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484671089", "session_id":"452381251"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Sunbury, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.2667", "longitude":"-82.8477", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452552429"},
          { "time":"1484677491", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 10:24am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.14.54.128", "uid":"909293689", "session_id":"452544559", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484677491", "session_id":"452544559"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8399", "longitude":"-73.9422", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452544559"},
          { "time":"1484676881", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 10:14am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"96.4.180.37", "uid":"2592323431", "session_id":"452528913", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484676881", "session_id":"452528913"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Collierville, Tennessee, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.0911", "longitude":"-89.6510", "hostname":"ena.net", "organization":"Education Networks Of America", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452528913"},
          { "time":"1484674963", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 9:42am", "time_total":"306", "ip_address":"209.59.65.105", "uid":"39297759", "session_id":"452480321", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484674963", "session_id":"452480321"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Road Town, Virgin Islands", "country_code":"vg", "latitude":"18.4167", "longitude":"-64.6167", "organization":"Cable & Wireless Dominica", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452480321"},
          { "time":"1484674897", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 9:41am", "time_total":"244", "ip_address":"68.45.213.71", "uid":"3248659068", "session_id":"452478627", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484674897", "session_id":"452478627"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Fort Wayne, Indiana, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.0483", "longitude":"-85.0801", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452478627"},
          { "time":"1484674045", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 9:27am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.222.63.90", "uid":"286739321", "session_id":"452456864", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484674045", "session_id":"452456864"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Tulare, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.1815", "longitude":"-119.3623", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452456864"},
          { "time":"1484674037", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 9:27am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.212.154", "uid":"3612993909", "session_id":"452456676", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1483888491", "session_id":"436239652"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://tpc.googlesyndication.com/", "referrer_domain":"tpc.googlesyndication.com", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0544", "longitude":"-118.2440", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452456676"},
          { "time":"1484673975", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 9:26am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"173.46.77.183", "uid":"2313699193", "session_id":"452455098", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484673975", "session_id":"452455098"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Louisville, Colorado, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.9558", "longitude":"-105.1683", "hostname":"updated.as8218.us", "organization":"Jasper Technologies", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452455098"},
          { "time":"1484673561", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 9:19am", "time_total":"121", "ip_address":"216.167.233.58", "uid":"1635833304", "session_id":"452444832", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1481038894", "session_id":"389789119"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/vocera/summit/value-received-broadening-customer-advocacy-experience", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1920x1080", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com/", "referrer_domain":"2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Kirkland Lake, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"48.1446", "longitude":"-80.0377", "hostname":"eastlink.ca", "organization":"Eastlink", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452444832"},
          { "time":"1484673490", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 9:18am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.199.9.47", "uid":"404877579", "session_id":"452443087", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484673490", "session_id":"452443087"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Middletown, Connecticut, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.5497", "longitude":"-72.6531", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452443087"},
          { "time":"1484672885", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 9:08am", "time_total":"360", "ip_address":"108.66.139.129", "uid":"741002392", "session_id":"452428367", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484672885", "session_id":"452428367"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"962x601", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"West Columbia, South Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.9900", "longitude":"-81.1016", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452428367"},
          { "time":"1484672565", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 9:02am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"172.56.18.130", "uid":"2444450327", "session_id":"452420557", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484672565", "session_id":"452420557"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 47.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"The Bronx, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8150", "longitude":"-73.9082", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452420557"},
          { "time":"1484672422", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 9am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"72.234.111.88", "uid":"1453834200", "session_id":"452417063", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484672422", "session_id":"452417063"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"414x736", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Hilo, Hawaii, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"19.6976", "longitude":"-155.1413", "hostname":"hawaiiantel.net", "organization":"Hawaiian Telcom", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452417063"},
          { "time":"1484672397", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 8:59am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.208.20.221", "uid":"3551329142", "session_id":"452416361", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484672397", "session_id":"452416361"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452416361"},
          { "time":"1484672364", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 8:59am", "time_total":"620", "ip_address":"66.87.130.167", "uid":"956268867", "session_id":"452415493", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484672364", "session_id":"452415493"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Norwalk, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.9071", "longitude":"-118.0767", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452415493"},
          { "time":"1484672090", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 8:54am", "time_total":"31", "ip_address":"174.194.137.30", "uid":"2733578441", "session_id":"452408497", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484672090", "session_id":"452408497"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Fayetteville, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.0570", "longitude":"-79.0147", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452408497"},
          { "time":"1484671754", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 8:49am", "time_total":"330", "ip_address":"32.211.2.25", "uid":"1761156833", "session_id":"452399531", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484671754", "session_id":"452399531"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Meriden, Connecticut, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.5372", "longitude":"-72.7801", "organization":"Frontier Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452399531"},
          { "time":"1484671284", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 8:41am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"172.58.14.184", "uid":"1225276442", "session_id":"452386407", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484671284", "session_id":"452386407"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 42.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.4484", "longitude":"-112.0740", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452386407"},
          { "time":"1484671206", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 8:40am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"154.5.174.153", "uid":"4287168852", "session_id":"452384392", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1483892978", "session_id":"436350397"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Vancouver, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"49.2603", "longitude":"-123.1460", "hostname":"telus.net", "organization":"Telus Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452384392"},
          { "time":"1484671156", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 8:39am", "time_total":"146", "ip_address":"139.59.235.246", "uid":"3421341779", "session_id":"452382913", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484671156", "session_id":"452382913"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 4.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"1080x1776", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Singapore, Singapore", "country_code":"sg", "latitude":"1.2931", "longitude":"103.8558", "organization":"Digital Ocean", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452382913"},
          { "time":"1484671089", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 8:38am", "time_total":"456", "ip_address":"24.31.185.223", "uid":"2781848127", "session_id":"452381251", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484671089", "session_id":"452381251"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Sunbury, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.2667", "longitude":"-82.8477", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452381251"},
          { "time":"1484671079", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 8:37am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"12.18.127.245", "uid":"3704364578", "session_id":"452380975", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484446802", "session_id":"448310965"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8130", "longitude":"-87.7134", "organization":"At&t Services", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452380975"},
          { "time":"1484670706", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 8:31am", "time_total":"270", "ip_address":"73.114.32.97", "uid":"1722879194", "session_id":"452371106", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484670706", "session_id":"452371106"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Malden, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.4281", "longitude":"-71.0546", "organization":"Xfinity Wifi", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452371106"},
          { "time":"1484670406", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 8:26am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"67.53.222.4", "uid":"4013071153", "session_id":"452363280", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484670406", "session_id":"452363280"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Hawaiian Ocean View, Hawaii, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"19.0613", "longitude":"-155.7170", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Road Runner Commercial", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452363280"},
          { "time":"1484669680", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 8:14am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"47.247.118.136", "uid":"1364351430", "session_id":"452343655", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484669680", "session_id":"452343655"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 4.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"720x1280", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Bhopal, India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"23.2667", "longitude":"77.4000", "organization":"Reliance Jio Infocomm Limited", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452343655"},
          { "time":"1484669481", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 8:11am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"98.176.188.183", "uid":"2986236360", "session_id":"452338244", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484669481", "session_id":"452338244"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Unknown mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Spring Valley, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.7170", "longitude":"-116.9950", "hostname":"cox.net", "organization":"Cox Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452338244"},
          { "time":"1484668562", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 7:56am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"5.212.187.159", "uid":"870811435", "session_id":"452314356", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1484144517", "session_id":"441934460"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Iran", "country_code":"ir", "latitude":"35.6961", "longitude":"51.4231", "organization":"Lte", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452314356"},
          { "time":"1484667567", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 7:39am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"73.185.90.184", "uid":"3120530984", "session_id":"452288813", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484667567", "session_id":"452288813"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Fresno, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.7683", "longitude":"-119.7628", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452288813"},
          { "time":"1484667318", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 7:35am", "time_total":"1626", "ip_address":"66.87.97.235", "uid":"3126752423", "session_id":"452282620", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484667318", "session_id":"452282620"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 51.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Dallas, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.8019", "longitude":"-96.7883", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452282620"},
          { "time":"1484665387", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 7:03am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"108.251.106.194", "uid":"1501433957", "session_id":"452233635", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484665387", "session_id":"452233635"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Corte Madera, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.9257", "longitude":"-122.5127", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452233635"},
          { "time":"1484665266", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 7:01am", "time_total":"86", "ip_address":"70.211.138.21", "uid":"401403038", "session_id":"452230717", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484665266", "session_id":"452230717"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Los Angeles, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0438", "longitude":"-118.2512", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452230717"},
          { "time":"1484664976", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 6:56am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.198.203.134", "uid":"3063500344", "session_id":"452223360", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484664976", "session_id":"452223360"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.4734", "longitude":"-79.9903", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452223360"},
          { "time":"1484664741", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 6:52am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.119.199.81", "uid":"1509421891", "session_id":"452217423", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484664741", "session_id":"452217423"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Whitby, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"43.8721", "longitude":"-78.9273", "hostname":"rogers.com", "organization":"Rogers Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452217423"},
          { "time":"1484664580", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 6:49am", "time_total":"30", "ip_address":"64.250.57.120", "uid":"1731901618", "session_id":"452213468", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484664580", "session_id":"452213468"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"La Cygne, Kansas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.3660", "longitude":"-94.7656", "hostname":"peoplestelecom.net", "organization":"Ptl-67", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452213468"},
          { "time":"1484663091", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 6:24am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"66.87.121.173", "uid":"3306710513", "session_id":"452176623", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484663091", "session_id":"452176623"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Houston, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"29.7270", "longitude":"-95.3613", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452176623"},
          { "time":"1484661915", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 6:05am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"99.66.228.187", "uid":"3681525558", "session_id":"452148264", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484661915", "session_id":"452148264"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 8.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Torrance, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.8669", "longitude":"-118.3312", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452148264"},
          { "time":"1484656508", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 4:35am", "time_total":"466", "ip_address":"70.122.239.110", "uid":"4282156646", "session_id":"452026789", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"10", "first_visit": {"time":"1476822083", "session_id":"335478898"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/vocera/summit/value-received-broadening-customer-advocacy-experience", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1440x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com/", "referrer_domain":"2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Dallas, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.8120", "longitude":"-96.8143", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452026789"},
          { "time":"1484656472", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 4:34am", "time_total":"670", "ip_address":"70.170.78.165", "uid":"3280234542", "session_id":"452025970", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"6", "first_visit": {"time":"1484231536", "session_id":"443771348"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Las Vegas, Nevada, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.1750", "longitude":"-115.1372", "hostname":"cox.net", "organization":"Cox Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=452025970"},
          { "time":"1484654380", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 3:59am", "time_total":"601", "ip_address":"70.122.239.110", "uid":"4282156646", "session_id":"451982138", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"10", "first_visit": {"time":"1476822083", "session_id":"335478898"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/vocera/summit/value-received-broadening-customer-advocacy-experience", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1440x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com/", "referrer_domain":"2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Dallas, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.8120", "longitude":"-96.8143", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451982138"},
          { "time":"1484652381", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 3:26am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"73.182.13.93", "uid":"632443347", "session_id":"451945027", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484614064", "session_id":"451394934"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Pooler, Georgia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.0957", "longitude":"-81.2531", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451945027"},
          { "time":"1484647748", "time_pretty":"Tue Jan 17 2017, 2:09am", "time_total":"122", "ip_address":"108.238.169.33", "uid":"2843160335", "session_id":"451864475", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484058769", "session_id":"439996276"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x480", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Lynwood, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.9251", "longitude":"-118.2032", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451864475"},
          { "time":"1484636635", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 11:03pm", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"96.237.253.85", "uid":"953059250", "session_id":"451705290", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484636635", "session_id":"451705290"}, "landing_page":"https://trunity.customerstories.net/umass-lowell/form-and-function-of-living-things-shea/umass-lowell-department-of-biology", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Windows 10", "screen_resolution":"1366x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://google.com/search?q=%5Bsecure+search%5D", "referrer_domain":"google.com", "referrer_search":"[secure search]", "referrer_type":"search", "geolocation":"Lynn, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.4733", "longitude":"-70.9419", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Fios", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451705290"},
          { "time":"1484636482", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 11:01pm", "time_total":"565", "ip_address":"139.59.215.186", "uid":"870811435", "session_id":"451703523", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1484144517", "session_id":"441934460"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Frankfurt am Main, Germany", "country_code":"de", "latitude":"50.1167", "longitude":"8.6833", "organization":"Digital Ocean", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451703523"},
          { "time":"1484635005", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:36pm", "time_total":"30", "ip_address":"139.59.138.145", "uid":"870811435", "session_id":"451686324", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1484144517", "session_id":"441934460"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Frankfurt am Main, Germany", "country_code":"de", "latitude":"50.1167", "longitude":"8.6833", "organization":"Digital Ocean", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451686324"},
          { "time":"1484624355", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 7:39pm", "time_total":"1362", "ip_address":"66.214.177.100", "uid":"829334053", "session_id":"451553193", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484622188", "session_id":"451522009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"California City, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.1509", "longitude":"-117.9215", "hostname":"charter.com", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451553193"},
          { "time":"1484622188", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 7:03pm", "time_total":"607", "ip_address":"66.214.177.100", "uid":"829334053", "session_id":"451522009", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484622188", "session_id":"451522009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"California City, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.1509", "longitude":"-117.9215", "hostname":"charter.com", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451522009"},
          { "time":"1484621586", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 6:53pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"73.17.129.133", "uid":"3601491892", "session_id":"451512610", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484621586", "session_id":"451512610"}, "landing_page":"https://trunity.customerstories.net/umass-lowell/form-and-function-of-living-things-shea/umass-lowell-department-of-biology", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://google.com/search?q=%5Bsecure+search%5D", "referrer_domain":"google.com", "referrer_search":"[secure search]", "referrer_type":"search", "geolocation":"Leominster, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.5244", "longitude":"-71.7657", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451512610"},
          { "time":"1484621121", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 6:45pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"98.209.57.83", "uid":"2341000511", "session_id":"451505925", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484621121", "session_id":"451505925"}, "landing_page":"https://trunity.customerstories.net/?product=integrating-concepts-in-biology-campell-heyer-paradise", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1440x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://trunity.com/trubook-integrating-concepts-in-biology-by-campbell-heyer-paradise.html", "referrer_domain":"trunity.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"East Lansing, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.7627", "longitude":"-84.4427", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451505925"},
          { "time":"1484620712", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 6:38pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"104.131.32.83", "uid":"3819781494", "session_id":"451499903", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484620712", "session_id":"451499903"}, "landing_page":"http://customerstories.net/", "web_browser":"Internet Explorer 10.0", "operating_system":"Windows 7", "screen_resolution":"1024x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7421", "longitude":"-74.0018", "organization":"Digital Ocean", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451499903"},
          { "time":"1484619770", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 6:22pm", "time_total":"29", "ip_address":"173.18.206.196", "uid":"760486802", "session_id":"451486026", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484612616", "session_id":"451370157"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Des Moines, Iowa, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.5833", "longitude":"-93.4973", "hostname":"mchsi.com", "organization":"Mediacom Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451486026"},
          { "time":"1484619685", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 6:21pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"103.53.199.88", "uid":"532824431", "session_id":"451484704", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"11", "first_visit": {"time":"1484319949", "session_id":"445796301"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Long Keng, Hong Kong", "country_code":"hk", "latitude":"22.2833", "longitude":"114.1500", "organization":"Digitalfyre Internet Solutions, Llc.", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451484704"},
          { "time":"1484617880", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 5:51pm", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"129.63.253.105", "uid":"2341378851", "session_id":"451457477", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484617880", "session_id":"451457477"}, "landing_page":"https://trunity.customerstories.net/life-on-this-rock/life-on-this-rock-shea/introduction-to-biology-for-students-majoring-in-other-fields", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 50.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://trunity.com/", "referrer_domain":"trunity.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Lowell, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.6523", "longitude":"-71.3506", "organization":"University Of Massachusetts - Lowell", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451457477"},
          { "time":"1484617489", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 5:44pm", "time_total":"492", "ip_address":"73.160.197.156", "uid":"462735920", "session_id":"451451252", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484616413", "session_id":"451433882"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"West Long Branch, New Jersey, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.2884", "longitude":"-74.0195", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451451252"},
          { "time":"1484616413", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 5:26pm", "time_total":"59", "ip_address":"73.160.197.156", "uid":"462735920", "session_id":"451433882", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484616413", "session_id":"451433882"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"West Long Branch, New Jersey, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.2884", "longitude":"-74.0195", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451433882"},
          { "time":"1484616066", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 5:21pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"199.47.67.52", "uid":"4282839094", "session_id":"451428547", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484593857", "session_id":"450965928"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Merino, Colorado, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6067", "longitude":"-103.4505", "hostname":"viaero.com", "organization":"Ne Colorado Cellular", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451428547"},
          { "time":"1484615384", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 5:09pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.205.235", "uid":"3730174898", "session_id":"451417356", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484615384", "session_id":"451417356"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Renton, Washington, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"47.4829", "longitude":"-122.2171", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451417356"},
          { "time":"1484614064", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 4:47pm", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"73.182.13.93", "uid":"632443347", "session_id":"451394934", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484614064", "session_id":"451394934"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Pooler, Georgia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.0957", "longitude":"-81.2531", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451394934"},
          { "time":"1484612616", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 4:23pm", "time_total":"33", "ip_address":"173.18.206.196", "uid":"760486802", "session_id":"451370157", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484612616", "session_id":"451370157"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Des Moines, Iowa, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.5833", "longitude":"-93.4973", "hostname":"mchsi.com", "organization":"Mediacom Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451370157"},
          { "time":"1484610026", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 3:40pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"74.210.201.38", "uid":"3109060750", "session_id":"451324228", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484610026", "session_id":"451324228"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"French", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Saint-hyacinthe, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"45.6567", "longitude":"-72.9237", "hostname":"cgocable.ca", "organization":"Cogeco Cable Holdings", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451324228"},
          { "time":"1484609799", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 3:36pm", "time_total":"65", "ip_address":"72.80.146.138", "uid":"203408883", "session_id":"451320121", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484609799", "session_id":"451320121"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Westbury, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7570", "longitude":"-73.5814", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Fios", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451320121"},
          { "time":"1484605869", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 2:31pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"72.169.96.244", "uid":"3507864063", "session_id":"451242868", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484605869", "session_id":"451242868"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8483", "longitude":"-87.6517", "hostname":"direcway.com", "organization":"Hughes Network Systems", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451242868"},
          { "time":"1484605480", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 2:24pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"73.199.134.130", "uid":"3160241543", "session_id":"451234677", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484605480", "session_id":"451234677"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 8.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Pleasantville, New Jersey, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.3914", "longitude":"-74.5182", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451234677"},
          { "time":"1484603350", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 1:49pm", "time_total":"309", "ip_address":"64.28.55.88", "uid":"798125322", "session_id":"451187332", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484603350", "session_id":"451187332"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Mobile, Alabama, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"30.6848", "longitude":"-88.0671", "organization":"Harbor Communications, Llc", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451187332"},
          { "time":"1484602206", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 1:30pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"24.230.245.67", "uid":"3488101263", "session_id":"451161605", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484602206", "session_id":"451161605"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"French", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Saint-hyacinthe, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"45.6139", "longitude":"-72.9912", "hostname":"cgocable.ca", "organization":"Cogeco Cable Holdings", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451161605"},
          { "time":"1484601616", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 1:20pm", "time_total":"433", "ip_address":"181.104.53.191", "uid":"2116561227", "session_id":"451147526", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484585830", "session_id":"450765067"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"Spanish", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Argentina", "country_code":"ar", "latitude":"-34.6033", "longitude":"-58.3817", "hostname":"telecom.net.ar", "organization":"Telecom Personal", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451147526"},
          { "time":"1484601292", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 1:14pm", "time_total":"119", "ip_address":"67.240.255.209", "uid":"2372552476", "session_id":"451139930", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"6", "first_visit": {"time":"1484010853", "session_id":"439050398"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 34.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Rochester, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"43.1858", "longitude":"-77.6024", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451139930"},
          { "time":"1484599917", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 12:51pm", "time_total":"244", "ip_address":"66.87.73.46", "uid":"3411431364", "session_id":"451107923", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484599917", "session_id":"451107923"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"St Louis, Missouri, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.6273", "longitude":"-90.1979", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451107923"},
          { "time":"1484597949", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 12:19pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"99.178.242.129", "uid":"1449944330", "session_id":"451062326", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484597949", "session_id":"451062326"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/sap/customer-case-studies/how-to-deploy-a-customer-reference-application-for-your-sales-team", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Windows 10", "screen_resolution":"1366x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://google.com/search?q=%5Bsecure+search%5D", "referrer_domain":"google.com", "referrer_search":"[secure search]", "referrer_type":"search", "geolocation":"Walnut Creek, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.9137", "longitude":"-122.0117", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t Internet Services", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451062326"},
          { "time":"1484597498", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 12:11pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"172.56.14.91", "uid":"748768277", "session_id":"451051952", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484597498", "session_id":"451051952"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Houston, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"29.7633", "longitude":"-95.3633", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451051952"},
          { "time":"1484597435", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 12:10pm", "time_total":"194", "ip_address":"107.77.213.135", "uid":"1385533284", "session_id":"451050554", "actions":"4", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484597435", "session_id":"451050554"}, "landing_page":"http://customerstories.net/", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0544", "longitude":"-118.2440", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451050554"},
          { "time":"1484595464", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 11:37am", "time_total":"102", "ip_address":"73.84.156.170", "uid":"237047521", "session_id":"451003602", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484595464", "session_id":"451003602"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Fort Lauderdale, Florida, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"26.1906", "longitude":"-80.1110", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=451003602"},
          { "time":"1484593857", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 11:10am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"199.47.67.52", "uid":"4282839094", "session_id":"450965928", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484593857", "session_id":"450965928"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Merino, Colorado, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6067", "longitude":"-103.4505", "hostname":"viaero.com", "organization":"Ne Colorado Cellular", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450965928"},
          { "time":"1484593410", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 11:03am", "time_total":"604", "ip_address":"173.46.77.181", "uid":"3623285732", "session_id":"450954905", "actions":"3", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484593410", "session_id":"450954905"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Louisville, Colorado, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.9558", "longitude":"-105.1683", "hostname":"updated.as8218.us", "organization":"Jasper Technologies", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450954905"},
          { "time":"1484593192", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:59am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"172.56.11.200", "uid":"3156612579", "session_id":"450949665", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484593192", "session_id":"450949665"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Detroit, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.3314", "longitude":"-83.0457", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450949665"},
          { "time":"1484592439", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:47am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"45.50.192.14", "uid":"2214277414", "session_id":"450931243", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484592439", "session_id":"450931243"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Fontana, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.1476", "longitude":"-117.4581", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450931243"},
          { "time":"1484592229", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:43am", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"107.77.232.217", "uid":"854668111", "session_id":"450926014", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484592229", "session_id":"450926014"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8596", "longitude":"-73.9314", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450926014"},
          { "time":"1484591706", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:35am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.221.7.232", "uid":"2570519353", "session_id":"450913361", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484591706", "session_id":"450913361"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8446", "longitude":"-87.7171", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450913361"},
          { "time":"1484591468", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:31am", "time_total":"240", "ip_address":"184.20.242.9", "uid":"2104723184", "session_id":"450907589", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484591468", "session_id":"450907589"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Exeter, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.2862", "longitude":"-119.0310", "organization":"Viasat Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450907589"},
          { "time":"1484591459", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:30am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"71.81.175.173", "uid":"3367120265", "session_id":"450907377", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484591459", "session_id":"450907377"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Yakima, Washington, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"46.7161", "longitude":"-120.4219", "hostname":"charter.com", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450907377"},
          { "time":"1484591209", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:26am", "time_total":"666", "ip_address":"73.192.247.175", "uid":"3323938370", "session_id":"450901369", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484591209", "session_id":"450901369"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Stockton, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.9579", "longitude":"-121.1287", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450901369"},
          { "time":"1484591110", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:25am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.209.149.11", "uid":"4260739080", "session_id":"450898894", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484591110", "session_id":"450898894"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Unknown mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Ilion, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.9689", "longitude":"-75.0890", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450898894"},
          { "time":"1484591030", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:23am", "time_total":"119", "ip_address":"66.87.9.119", "uid":"2591775812", "session_id":"450896907", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484591030", "session_id":"450896907"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Newark, New Jersey, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7918", "longitude":"-74.2452", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450896907"},
          { "time":"1484590846", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:20am", "time_total":"79", "ip_address":"76.14.52.12", "uid":"927907641", "session_id":"450892301", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"22", "first_visit": {"time":"1462383504", "session_id":"131836516"}, "landing_page":"http://customerstories.net/", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1440x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "geolocation":"Redwood City, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.4914", "longitude":"-122.2110", "hostname":"astound.net", "organization":"Wave Broadband", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450892301"},
          { "time":"1484590725", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:18am", "time_total":"653", "ip_address":"172.56.28.45", "uid":"1721785442", "session_id":"450889335", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484590725", "session_id":"450889335"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 28.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x534", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.0192", "longitude":"-75.0940", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450889335"},
          { "time":"1484590644", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:17am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.211.135.173", "uid":"2745612401", "session_id":"450887431", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484590644", "session_id":"450887431"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Los Angeles, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.1073", "longitude":"-118.3719", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450887431"},
          { "time":"1484590505", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:15am", "time_total":"401", "ip_address":"98.151.169.43", "uid":"3206597884", "session_id":"450883997", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484590505", "session_id":"450883997"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450883997"},
          { "time":"1484590479", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:14am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"205.201.73.59", "uid":"2309661453", "session_id":"450883348", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484590479", "session_id":"450883348"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 45.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"1024x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"San Angelo, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"31.5468", "longitude":"-100.5610", "hostname":"suddenlink.net", "organization":"Suddenlink Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450883348"},
          { "time":"1484590094", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:08am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"172.58.73.196", "uid":"148251844", "session_id":"450873905", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484590094", "session_id":"450873905"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Las Vegas, Nevada, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.0877", "longitude":"-115.1485", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450873905"},
          { "time":"1484590048", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:07am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"184.156.212.168", "uid":"695512150", "session_id":"450872854", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484590048", "session_id":"450872854"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Clarksville, Arkansas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.5071", "longitude":"-93.5119", "hostname":"centurytel.net", "organization":"Centurylink", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450872854"},
          { "time":"1484589889", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10:04am", "time_total":"64", "ip_address":"107.77.232.108", "uid":"292296845", "session_id":"450868919", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484589889", "session_id":"450868919"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 51.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8596", "longitude":"-73.9314", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450868919"},
          { "time":"1484589636", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 10am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"200.113.234.39", "uid":"1204810112", "session_id":"450862414", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484589636", "session_id":"450862414"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Port-au-Prince, Haiti", "country_code":"ht", "latitude":"18.5392", "longitude":"-72.3350", "organization":"Ict-wimax Pool8", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450862414"},
          { "time":"1484589355", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 9:55am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"50.24.134.183", "uid":"3357100161", "session_id":"450855426", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484589355", "session_id":"450855426"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"College Station, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"30.5670", "longitude":"-96.2837", "hostname":"suddenlink.net", "organization":"Suddenlink Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450855426"},
          { "time":"1484589134", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 9:52am", "time_total":"912", "ip_address":"70.199.96.145", "uid":"1924126775", "session_id":"450849745", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484589134", "session_id":"450849745"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7605", "longitude":"-73.9933", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450849745"},
          { "time":"1484589112", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 9:51am", "time_total":"121", "ip_address":"24.192.174.69", "uid":"4120967235", "session_id":"450849216", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484589112", "session_id":"450849216"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Sterling Heights, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.5988", "longitude":"-83.0104", "hostname":"wideopenwest.com", "organization":"Wideopenwest", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450849216"},
          { "time":"1484589008", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 9:50am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"68.53.238.224", "uid":"1163599948", "session_id":"450846436", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484589008", "session_id":"450846436"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"534x320", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Benton, Tennessee, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.1689", "longitude":"-84.6111", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450846436"},
          { "time":"1484588839", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 9:47am", "time_total":"619", "ip_address":"76.14.52.12", "uid":"927907641", "session_id":"450842203", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"22", "first_visit": {"time":"1462383504", "session_id":"131836516"}, "landing_page":"http://customerstories.net/", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1440x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "geolocation":"Redwood City, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.4914", "longitude":"-122.2110", "hostname":"astound.net", "organization":"Wave Broadband", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450842203"},
          { "time":"1484588714", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 9:45am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"99.243.206.71", "uid":"158602529", "session_id":"450839323", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484588714", "session_id":"450839323"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Mississauga, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"43.5637", "longitude":"-79.7202", "organization":"Rogers Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450839323"},
          { "time":"1484587308", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 9:21am", "time_total":"59", "ip_address":"107.185.238.99", "uid":"2957044623", "session_id":"450803832", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484587308", "session_id":"450803832"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Carson, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.8267", "longitude":"-118.2607", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450803832"},
          { "time":"1484587016", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 9:16am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"172.58.136.209", "uid":"4239823763", "session_id":"450796155", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484587016", "session_id":"450796155"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.5783", "longitude":"-90.6666", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450796155"},
          { "time":"1484585830", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 8:57am", "time_total":"396", "ip_address":"181.104.57.63", "uid":"2116561227", "session_id":"450765067", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484585830", "session_id":"450765067"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"Spanish", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Argentina", "country_code":"ar", "latitude":"-34.6033", "longitude":"-58.3817", "hostname":"telecom.net.ar", "organization":"Telecom Personal", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450765067"},
          { "time":"1484584648", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 8:37am", "time_total":"59", "ip_address":"63.152.103.103", "uid":"951169529", "session_id":"450733253", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484584648", "session_id":"450733253"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Marion, Iowa, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.0604", "longitude":"-91.5858", "hostname":"qwest.net", "organization":"Centurylink", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450733253"},
          { "time":"1484584352", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 8:32am", "time_total":"28", "ip_address":"73.93.153.99", "uid":"3067725622", "session_id":"450725391", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484504743", "session_id":"449246481"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://m.wenxuecity.com/", "referrer_domain":"m.wenxuecity.com", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Fremont, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.5079", "longitude":"-121.9599", "organization":"Xfinity Wifi", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450725391"},
          { "time":"1484584171", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 8:29am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.106.158.191", "uid":"36858585", "session_id":"450720558", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484584171", "session_id":"450720558"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Morehead City, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.7386", "longitude":"-76.7677", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450720558"},
          { "time":"1484582349", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 7:59am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.114.29.193", "uid":"411470181", "session_id":"450673599", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484582349", "session_id":"450673599"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"47.5500", "longitude":"-52.6667", "hostname":"rogers.com", "organization":"Rogers Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450673599"},
          { "time":"1484580252", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 7:24am", "time_total":"632", "ip_address":"66.87.114.29", "uid":"818848088", "session_id":"450620023", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484241209", "session_id":"444080889"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"732x412", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Ecorse, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.2496", "longitude":"-83.1436", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450620023"},
          { "time":"1484577003", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 6:30am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"216.246.166.72", "uid":"3431944649", "session_id":"450540483", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484508177", "session_id":"449323677"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Kissimmee, Florida, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"28.3047", "longitude":"-81.4167", "organization":"Summit Broadband", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450540483"},
          { "time":"1484572287", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 5:11am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"69.12.109.145", "uid":"1159775853", "session_id":"450434300", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484261243", "session_id":"444671760"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Roseau, Dominica", "country_code":"dm", "latitude":"15.3000", "longitude":"-61.4000", "organization":"Sat Telecommunications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450434300"},
          { "time":"1484572108", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 5:08am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"172.56.28.30", "uid":"2163338794", "session_id":"450430536", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484572108", "session_id":"450430536"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"414x736", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.0192", "longitude":"-75.0940", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450430536"},
          { "time":"1484571515", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 4:58am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"67.8.231.249", "uid":"3230475524", "session_id":"450418220", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484507025", "session_id":"449298841"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Satellite Beach, Florida, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"28.1761", "longitude":"-80.5901", "hostname":"bhn.net", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450418220"},
          { "time":"1484562764", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 2:32am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"66.102.8.135", "uid":"2308055551", "session_id":"450249909", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484562764", "session_id":"450249909"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://google.co.in/search?q=%5Bsecure+search%5D", "referrer_domain":"google.co.in", "referrer_search":"[secure search]", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"28.0222", "longitude":"-81.7329", "hostname":"google.com", "organization":"Google", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450249909"},
          { "time":"1484561980", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 2:19am", "time_total":"31", "ip_address":"107.77.209.155", "uid":"1133910472", "session_id":"450235434", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1484521751", "session_id":"449628945"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 45.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8500", "longitude":"-87.6500", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450235434"},
          { "time":"1484557083", "time_pretty":"Mon Jan 16 2017, 12:58am", "time_total":"2168", "ip_address":"107.77.209.155", "uid":"1133910472", "session_id":"450149768", "actions":"5", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1484521751", "session_id":"449628945"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 45.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8500", "longitude":"-87.6500", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450149768"},
          { "time":"1484552746", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 11:45pm", "time_total":"642", "ip_address":"49.34.242.88", "uid":"680212961", "session_id":"450085538", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484552746", "session_id":"450085538"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Latipur, India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"22.6167", "longitude":"70.5333", "organization":"Reliance Jio Infocomm Ltd", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450085538"},
          { "time":"1484549012", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 10:43pm", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"49.34.58.189", "uid":"532824431", "session_id":"450035754", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"11", "first_visit": {"time":"1484319949", "session_id":"445796301"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Navsari, India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"20.8500", "longitude":"72.9167", "organization":"Reliance Jio Infocomm Ltd", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=450035754"},
          { "time":"1484544058", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 9:20pm", "time_total":"374", "ip_address":"107.77.209.155", "uid":"1133910472", "session_id":"449973468", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1484521751", "session_id":"449628945"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 45.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8500", "longitude":"-87.6500", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449973468"},
          { "time":"1484542687", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 8:58pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"50.143.129.107", "uid":"1446025430", "session_id":"449955687", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484167141", "session_id":"442516692"}, "landing_page":"http://customerstories.net/plans", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1360x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "geolocation":"San Rafael, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.9719", "longitude":"-122.5023", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449955687"},
          { "time":"1484538292", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 7:44pm", "time_total":"1367", "ip_address":"107.77.205.48", "uid":"3503541312", "session_id":"449897210", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484538292", "session_id":"449897210"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.9597", "longitude":"-75.1968", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449897210"},
          { "time":"1484538168", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 7:42pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"71.9.128.231", "uid":"644259470", "session_id":"449895490", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484536485", "session_id":"449871245"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 8.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Redding, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6083", "longitude":"-122.4618", "hostname":"charter.com", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449895490"},
          { "time":"1484536485", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 7:14pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"71.9.128.231", "uid":"644259470", "session_id":"449871245", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484536485", "session_id":"449871245"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 8.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Redding, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6083", "longitude":"-122.4618", "hostname":"charter.com", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449871245"},
          { "time":"1484535579", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:59pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"69.1.25.57", "uid":"2563562819", "session_id":"449857730", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484535579", "session_id":"449857730"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Madison, Alabama, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.7135", "longitude":"-86.7421", "hostname":"knology.net", "organization":"Wideopenwest", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449857730"},
          { "time":"1484535567", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:59pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"65.27.5.14", "uid":"2507030868", "session_id":"449857570", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484535567", "session_id":"449857570"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Cincinnati, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.1579", "longitude":"-84.5966", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449857570"},
          { "time":"1484535561", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:59pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"98.160.185.101", "uid":"1059231152", "session_id":"449857482", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484409719", "session_id":"447543838"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"North Las Vegas, Nevada, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.2729", "longitude":"-115.1333", "hostname":"cox.net", "organization":"Cox Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449857482"},
          { "time":"1484534931", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:48pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"67.240.255.209", "uid":"2372552476", "session_id":"449848138", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"6", "first_visit": {"time":"1484010853", "session_id":"439050398"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 34.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Rochester, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"43.1858", "longitude":"-77.6024", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449848138"},
          { "time":"1484533383", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:23pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.209.155", "uid":"1133910472", "session_id":"449824740", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1484521751", "session_id":"449628945"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 45.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8500", "longitude":"-87.6500", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449824740"},
          { "time":"1484532852", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:14pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"169.149.48.118", "uid":"2740850861", "session_id":"449816525", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484532852", "session_id":"449816525"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Jammu, India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"32.7333", "longitude":"74.8667", "organization":"Reliance Jio Infocomm Ltd", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449816525"},
          { "time":"1484532086", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:01pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"76.22.123.202", "uid":"155225846", "session_id":"449804515", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1483041978", "session_id":"419411342"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 5.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://tpc.googlesyndication.com/", "referrer_domain":"tpc.googlesyndication.com", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Seattle, Washington, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"47.6854", "longitude":"-122.2872", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449804515"},
          { "time":"1484532064", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:01pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"221.241.189.165", "uid":"3533258783", "session_id":"449804134", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484532064", "session_id":"449804134"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Windows 7", "screen_resolution":"1920x1080", "javascript":"1", "language":"Japanese", "referrer_url":"http://google.co.jp/search?q=%5Bsecure+search%5D", "referrer_domain":"google.co.jp", "referrer_search":"[secure search]", "referrer_type":"search", "geolocation":"Tokyo, Japan", "country_code":"jp", "latitude":"35.6850", "longitude":"139.7514", "hostname":"ucom.ne.jp", "organization":"Arteria Networks Corporation", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449804134"},
          { "time":"1484531314", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 5:48pm", "time_total":"720", "ip_address":"107.77.209.155", "uid":"1133910472", "session_id":"449791962", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1484521751", "session_id":"449628945"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 45.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8500", "longitude":"-87.6500", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449791962"},
          { "time":"1484530042", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 5:27pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"69.146.177.71", "uid":"3228075699", "session_id":"449771802", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484410244", "session_id":"447555738"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 8.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"La Junta, Colorado, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.8463", "longitude":"-103.5836", "hostname":"bresnan.net", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449771802"},
          { "time":"1484529174", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 5:12pm", "time_total":"93", "ip_address":"66.38.78.221", "uid":"1039571207", "session_id":"449757646", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484529174", "session_id":"449757646"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Russell Springs, Kentucky, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.0707", "longitude":"-85.0479", "hostname":"duo-county.com", "organization":"Bluegrass Network Llc", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449757646"},
          { "time":"1484529141", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 5:12pm", "time_total":"360", "ip_address":"98.5.205.245", "uid":"1077230262", "session_id":"449757207", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484529141", "session_id":"449757207"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Buffalo, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.8864", "longitude":"-78.8784", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449757207"},
          { "time":"1484524908", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 4:01pm", "time_total":"477", "ip_address":"107.77.209.155", "uid":"1133910472", "session_id":"449686644", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1484521751", "session_id":"449628945"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 45.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8500", "longitude":"-87.6500", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449686644"},
          { "time":"1484524603", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 3:56pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"73.79.151.205", "uid":"1086662688", "session_id":"449681016", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484524603", "session_id":"449681016"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 7.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x480", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.4223", "longitude":"-79.9791", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449681016"},
          { "time":"1484523934", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 3:45pm", "time_total":"55", "ip_address":"96.41.97.161", "uid":"3637130893", "session_id":"449669011", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484523934", "session_id":"449669011"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Azusa, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.1748", "longitude":"-117.8751", "hostname":"charter.com", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449669011"},
          { "time":"1484521751", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 3:09pm", "time_total":"240", "ip_address":"107.77.209.155", "uid":"1133910472", "session_id":"449628945", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1484521751", "session_id":"449628945"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 45.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8500", "longitude":"-87.6500", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449628945"},
          { "time":"1484520844", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 2:54pm", "time_total":"376", "ip_address":"24.91.223.121", "uid":"605855059", "session_id":"449611202", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"9", "first_visit": {"time":"1482514748", "session_id":"411204811"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://officechai.com/news/elon-musk-receives-product-suggestion-twitter-tesla-implements-6-days-later/", "referrer_domain":"officechai.com", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Rehoboth, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8428", "longitude":"-71.2455", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449611202"},
          { "time":"1484520739", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 2:52pm", "time_total":"335", "ip_address":"174.209.17.200", "uid":"3306504189", "session_id":"449609036", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"5", "first_visit": {"time":"1483493888", "session_id":"428135894"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449609036"},
          { "time":"1484520379", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 2:46pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"76.21.117.176", "uid":"3067725622", "session_id":"449602151", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484504743", "session_id":"449246481"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://m.wenxuecity.com/", "referrer_domain":"m.wenxuecity.com", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Palo Alto, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.4419", "longitude":"-122.1430", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449602151"},
          { "time":"1484519996", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 2:39pm", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"66.25.137.220", "uid":"2588095141", "session_id":"449594696", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1482975868", "session_id":"418160856"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"San Antonio, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"29.4616", "longitude":"-98.5735", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449594696"},
          { "time":"1484519102", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 2:25pm", "time_total":"65", "ip_address":"76.21.117.176", "uid":"3067725622", "session_id":"449575721", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484504743", "session_id":"449246481"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://m.wenxuecity.com/", "referrer_domain":"m.wenxuecity.com", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Palo Alto, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.4419", "longitude":"-122.1430", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449575721"},
          { "time":"1484518677", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 2:17pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"216.218.66.193", "uid":"1432632850", "session_id":"449566419", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484518677", "session_id":"449566419"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Sardinia, South Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.8343", "longitude":"-80.0828", "organization":"Farmers Telephone Cooperative", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449566419"},
          { "time":"1484512860", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 12:41pm", "time_total":"69", "ip_address":"49.34.120.0", "uid":"532824431", "session_id":"449431875", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"11", "first_visit": {"time":"1484319949", "session_id":"445796301"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Ahmedabad, India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"23.0333", "longitude":"72.6167", "organization":"Reliance Jio Infocomm Ltd", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449431875"},
          { "time":"1484510168", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 11:56am", "time_total":"660", "ip_address":"75.108.77.191", "uid":"1919645990", "session_id":"449366526", "actions":"3", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484510168", "session_id":"449366526"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New Bern, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.1427", "longitude":"-77.1630", "hostname":"suddenlink.net", "organization":"Suddenlink Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449366526"},
          { "time":"1484509211", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 11:40am", "time_total":"30", "ip_address":"174.100.247.240", "uid":"3951628357", "session_id":"449344278", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484496342", "session_id":"449055596"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Erie, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.0577", "longitude":"-80.0434", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449344278"},
          { "time":"1484508491", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 11:28am", "time_total":"1017", "ip_address":"173.46.78.156", "uid":"2588095141", "session_id":"449329718", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1482975868", "session_id":"418160856"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Louisville, Colorado, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.9558", "longitude":"-105.1683", "hostname":"updated.as8218.us", "organization":"Jasper Technologies", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449329718"},
          { "time":"1484508177", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 11:22am", "time_total":"44", "ip_address":"216.246.166.72", "uid":"3431944649", "session_id":"449323677", "actions":"5", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484508177", "session_id":"449323677"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Kissimmee, Florida, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"28.3047", "longitude":"-81.4167", "organization":"Summit Broadband", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449323677"},
          { "time":"1484507207", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 11:06am", "time_total":"162", "ip_address":"50.130.86.4", "uid":"3982824522", "session_id":"449302914", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484507207", "session_id":"449302914"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Tupelo, Mississippi, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.2217", "longitude":"-88.7688", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449302914"},
          { "time":"1484507025", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 11:03am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"67.8.231.249", "uid":"3230475524", "session_id":"449298841", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484507025", "session_id":"449298841"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Satellite Beach, Florida, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"28.1761", "longitude":"-80.5901", "hostname":"bhn.net", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449298841"},
          { "time":"1484506971", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 11:02am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"49.34.254.202", "uid":"532824431", "session_id":"449297744", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"11", "first_visit": {"time":"1484319949", "session_id":"445796301"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Anand, India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"22.5667", "longitude":"72.9333", "organization":"Reliance Jio Infocomm Ltd", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449297744"},
          { "time":"1484506345", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 10:52am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"173.46.77.168", "uid":"2385899689", "session_id":"449283362", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484417981", "session_id":"447734134"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Louisville, Colorado, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.9558", "longitude":"-105.1683", "hostname":"updated.as8218.us", "organization":"Jasper Technologies", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449283362"},
          { "time":"1484505794", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 10:43am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.224.155", "uid":"1376589079", "session_id":"449270652", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484500097", "session_id":"449139132"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8596", "longitude":"-73.9314", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449270652"},
          { "time":"1484504975", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 10:29am", "time_total":"379", "ip_address":"174.199.12.54", "uid":"2810639607", "session_id":"449251960", "actions":"3", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484504975", "session_id":"449251960"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Middletown, Connecticut, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.5497", "longitude":"-72.6531", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449251960"},
          { "time":"1484504743", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 10:25am", "time_total":"60", "ip_address":"76.21.117.176", "uid":"3067725622", "session_id":"449246481", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484504743", "session_id":"449246481"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://m.wenxuecity.com/", "referrer_domain":"m.wenxuecity.com", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Palo Alto, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.4419", "longitude":"-122.1430", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449246481"},
          { "time":"1484503975", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 10:12am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"108.21.201.36", "uid":"16685595", "session_id":"449228771", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484503975", "session_id":"449228771"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"The Bronx, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8195", "longitude":"-73.9209", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Fios", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449228771"},
          { "time":"1484501951", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 9:39am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.255.205.60", "uid":"4181663290", "session_id":"449181679", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484337710", "session_id":"446307348"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449181679"},
          { "time":"1484501814", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 9:36am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"99.20.181.50", "session_id":"449178434", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484501814", "session_id":"449178434"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Woodstock, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.3222", "longitude":"-88.4671", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449178434"},
          { "time":"1484501612", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 9:33am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.232.79", "uid":"4251756500", "session_id":"449173661", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484501612", "session_id":"449173661"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8596", "longitude":"-73.9314", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449173661"},
          { "time":"1484501607", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 9:33am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.213.168.161", "uid":"1659801358", "session_id":"449173537", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484501607", "session_id":"449173537"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"414x736", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8802", "longitude":"-87.7566", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449173537"},
          { "time":"1484500440", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 9:14am", "time_total":"30", "ip_address":"166.182.81.112", "uid":"3277840697", "session_id":"449146855", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484500440", "session_id":"449146855"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 50.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"Spanish", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "organization":"Wireless Data Service Provider Corporation", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449146855"},
          { "time":"1484500353", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 9:12am", "time_total":"252", "ip_address":"174.221.131.208", "uid":"481804561", "session_id":"449144951", "actions":"3", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484500353", "session_id":"449144951"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.6966", "longitude":"-87.6637", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449144951"},
          { "time":"1484500178", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 9:09am", "time_total":"605", "ip_address":"73.114.35.146", "uid":"675278328", "session_id":"449140872", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484500178", "session_id":"449140872"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Somerville, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.4019", "longitude":"-71.1193", "organization":"Xfinity Wifi", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449140872"},
          { "time":"1484500097", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 9:08am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.224.155", "uid":"1376589079", "session_id":"449139132", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484500097", "session_id":"449139132"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8596", "longitude":"-73.9314", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449139132"},
          { "time":"1484499824", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 9:03am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"65.93.92.106", "uid":"2373872267", "session_id":"449132607", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484499824", "session_id":"449132607"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Mississauga, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"43.5647", "longitude":"-79.5852", "hostname":"bell.ca", "organization":"Bell Canada", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449132607"},
          { "time":"1484499344", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 8:55am", "time_total":"359", "ip_address":"172.56.19.23", "uid":"2987269084", "session_id":"449121307", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484499344", "session_id":"449121307"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"570x320", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"The Bronx, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8690", "longitude":"-73.9023", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449121307"},
          { "time":"1484499042", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 8:50am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"5.133.24.62", "uid":"3997390186", "session_id":"449114491", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484499042", "session_id":"449114491"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Gaza, Palestinian Territory", "country_code":"ps", "latitude":"31.5000", "longitude":"34.4667", "organization":"Ultranet For Communication And Information Technol", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449114491"},
          { "time":"1484498898", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 8:48am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"69.136.132.252", "uid":"2903286732", "session_id":"449111081", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484409612", "session_id":"447541275"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 34.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Detroit, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.4255", "longitude":"-83.2533", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Xfinity Wifi", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449111081"},
          { "time":"1484498325", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 8:38am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.200.187", "uid":"2067202510", "session_id":"449097847", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484494819", "session_id":"449022974"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Sachse, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.9685", "longitude":"-96.5821", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449097847"},
          { "time":"1484497546", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 8:25am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"72.74.204.23", "uid":"3826274501", "session_id":"449080325", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484497546", "session_id":"449080325"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Brockton, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.0796", "longitude":"-71.0382", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Internet Services", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449080325"},
          { "time":"1484497514", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 8:25am", "time_total":"30", "ip_address":"72.74.204.23", "uid":"2525780261", "session_id":"449079660", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484497514", "session_id":"449079660"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Brockton, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.0796", "longitude":"-71.0382", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Internet Services", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449079660"},
          { "time":"1484497487", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 8:24am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.255.205.118", "uid":"2559304392", "session_id":"449079105", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484497487", "session_id":"449079105"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449079105"},
          { "time":"1484496342", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 8:05am", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"174.100.247.240", "uid":"3951628357", "session_id":"449055596", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484496342", "session_id":"449055596"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Erie, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.0577", "longitude":"-80.0434", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449055596"},
          { "time":"1484496120", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 8:02am", "time_total":"29", "ip_address":"66.229.9.168", "uid":"2367840658", "session_id":"449051142", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484496120", "session_id":"449051142"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Hollywood, Florida, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"25.9829", "longitude":"-80.2794", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449051142"},
          { "time":"1484495809", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 7:56am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"172.56.15.134", "uid":"2390146108", "session_id":"449044574", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484495809", "session_id":"449044574"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Unknown mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Houston, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"29.7633", "longitude":"-95.3633", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449044574"},
          { "time":"1484494819", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 7:40am", "time_total":"177", "ip_address":"107.77.200.187", "uid":"2067202510", "session_id":"449022974", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484494819", "session_id":"449022974"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Sachse, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.9685", "longitude":"-96.5821", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449022974"},
          { "time":"1484494027", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 7:27am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"188.57.180.165", "uid":"1491284696", "session_id":"449005796", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484494027", "session_id":"449005796"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"Arabic", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Turkey", "country_code":"tr", "latitude":"41.0214", "longitude":"28.9948", "organization":"Turkcell", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=449005796"},
          { "time":"1484493448", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 7:17am", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"67.174.123.53", "uid":"717679453", "session_id":"448993485", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484493448", "session_id":"448993485"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Breckenridge, Colorado, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.4678", "longitude":"-105.9962", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448993485"},
          { "time":"1484492646", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 7:04am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"172.249.193.19", "uid":"3573305357", "session_id":"448977635", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484492646", "session_id":"448977635"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"South Gate, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.9547", "longitude":"-118.2120", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448977635"},
          { "time":"1484491877", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:51am", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"66.87.114.29", "uid":"818848088", "session_id":"448962470", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484241209", "session_id":"444080889"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"732x412", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Ecorse, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.2496", "longitude":"-83.1436", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448962470"},
          { "time":"1484491482", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:44am", "time_total":"1359", "ip_address":"66.87.64.54", "uid":"258532355", "session_id":"448954431", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484491482", "session_id":"448954431"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Los Angeles, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0093", "longitude":"-118.2584", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448954431"},
          { "time":"1484491240", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:40am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"47.18.226.63", "uid":"1167048337", "session_id":"448949461", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484491240", "session_id":"448949461"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"414x736", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"The Bronx, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8760", "longitude":"-73.8716", "hostname":"optonline.net", "organization":"Optimum Online", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448949461"},
          { "time":"1484491210", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:40am", "time_total":"125", "ip_address":"123.147.246.135", "uid":"2999748147", "session_id":"448948883", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484491210", "session_id":"448948883"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 4.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"720x1280", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chongqing, China", "country_code":"cn", "latitude":"29.5628", "longitude":"106.5528", "organization":"China Unicom Liaoning", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448948883"},
          { "time":"1484490563", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:29am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"98.67.0.102", "uid":"1569064047", "session_id":"448936225", "actions":"3", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484490563", "session_id":"448936225"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Florence, South Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.2125", "longitude":"-79.8206", "hostname":"bellsouth.net", "organization":"At&t Internet Services", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448936225"},
          { "time":"1484490279", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:24am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.255.200.154", "uid":"3975321094", "session_id":"448930474", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484490279", "session_id":"448930474"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448930474"},
          { "time":"1484489637", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:13am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"172.58.152.81", "uid":"2825351422", "session_id":"448917660", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484489637", "session_id":"448917660"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Atlanta, Georgia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.7453", "longitude":"-84.3829", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448917660"},
          { "time":"1484489047", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 6:04am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"76.8.109.169", "uid":"3672371842", "session_id":"448906386", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484489047", "session_id":"448906386"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 30.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"1024x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Autryville, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.0313", "longitude":"-78.6262", "hostname":"intrstar.net", "organization":"Star Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448906386"},
          { "time":"1484484685", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 4:51am", "time_total":"244", "ip_address":"49.34.177.111", "uid":"532824431", "session_id":"448827778", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"11", "first_visit": {"time":"1484319949", "session_id":"445796301"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Ahmedabad, India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"23.0333", "longitude":"72.6167", "organization":"Reliance Jio Infocomm Ltd", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448827778"},
          { "time":"1484483591", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 4:33am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"65.185.162.136", "uid":"3760032937", "session_id":"448809699", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484323096", "session_id":"445892750"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x534", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Malvern, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6841", "longitude":"-81.1713", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448809699"},
          { "time":"1484482597", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 4:16am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.205.151", "uid":"4026868225", "session_id":"448794275", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484482597", "session_id":"448794275"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Renton, Washington, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"47.4829", "longitude":"-122.2171", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448794275"},
          { "time":"1484480291", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 3:38am", "time_total":"239", "ip_address":"66.87.115.234", "uid":"3937603169", "session_id":"448758083", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484480291", "session_id":"448758083"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Detroit, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.3314", "longitude":"-83.0457", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448758083"},
          { "time":"1484478379", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 3:06am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"96.41.87.208", "uid":"1236207235", "session_id":"448729832", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1483625314", "session_id":"430884030"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Long Beach, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.7816", "longitude":"-118.1859", "hostname":"charter.com", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448729832"},
          { "time":"1484467501", "time_pretty":"Sun Jan 15 2017, 12:05am", "time_total":"122", "ip_address":"178.135.199.73", "uid":"3082053699", "session_id":"448583010", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484157681", "session_id":"442286225"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Beirut, Lebanon", "country_code":"lb", "latitude":"33.8719", "longitude":"35.5097", "organization":"Libantelecom", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448583010"},
          { "time":"1484463388", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 10:56pm", "time_total":"30", "ip_address":"108.71.92.56", "uid":"2638452663", "session_id":"448534568", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"152", "first_visit": {"time":"1449517556", "session_id":"38718927"}, "landing_page":"https://trunity.customerstories.net/integrating-concepts-in-biology/integrating-concepts-in-biology-campell-heyer-paradise/integrating-concepts-in-biology", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1680x1050", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "geolocation":"Palo Alto, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.4429", "longitude":"-122.1514", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448534568"},
          { "time":"1484462317", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 10:38pm", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"208.54.36.242", "uid":"2372552476", "session_id":"448522091", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"6", "first_visit": {"time":"1484010853", "session_id":"439050398"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 34.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Woonsocket, Rhode Island, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.0029", "longitude":"-71.5148", "hostname":"tmodns.net", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448522091"},
          { "time":"1484455224", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:40pm", "time_total":"247", "ip_address":"70.211.138.198", "uid":"1236207235", "session_id":"448432410", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1483625314", "session_id":"430884030"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Los Angeles, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0438", "longitude":"-118.2512", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448432410"},
          { "time":"1484451504", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 7:38pm", "time_total":"602", "ip_address":"49.34.71.220", "uid":"532824431", "session_id":"448381111", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"11", "first_visit": {"time":"1484319949", "session_id":"445796301"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Ahmedabad, India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"23.0333", "longitude":"72.6167", "organization":"Reliance Jio Infocomm Ltd", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448381111"},
          { "time":"1484449296", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 7:01pm", "time_total":"314", "ip_address":"70.211.138.198", "uid":"1236207235", "session_id":"448347213", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1483625314", "session_id":"430884030"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Los Angeles, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0438", "longitude":"-118.2512", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448347213"},
          { "time":"1484448847", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:54pm", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"185.89.248.21", "uid":"532824431", "session_id":"448340049", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"11", "first_visit": {"time":"1484319949", "session_id":"445796301"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Istanbul, Turkey", "country_code":"tr", "latitude":"41.0186", "longitude":"28.9647", "organization":"Giglinx Global", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448340049"},
          { "time":"1484447139", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:25pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"98.20.214.204", "uid":"2942451884", "session_id":"448316068", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484447139", "session_id":"448316068"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Dahlonega, Georgia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.5728", "longitude":"-84.0263", "hostname":"windstream.net", "organization":"Windstream Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448316068"},
          { "time":"1484446802", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:20pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"73.210.48.222", "uid":"3704364578", "session_id":"448310965", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484446802", "session_id":"448310965"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8471", "longitude":"-87.6248", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448310965"},
          { "time":"1484446724", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:18pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.208.66.43", "uid":"1306544581", "session_id":"448309755", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484446724", "session_id":"448309755"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Elizabeth, New Jersey, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6728", "longitude":"-74.1790", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448309755"},
          { "time":"1484445486", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 5:58pm", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"46.99.106.249", "uid":"4053066141", "session_id":"448290623", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"14", "first_visit": {"time":"1484151392", "session_id":"442121009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Albania", "country_code":"al", "latitude":"41.0000", "longitude":"20.0000", "organization":"Ipko Telecommunications Llc", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448290623"},
          { "time":"1484442123", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 5:02pm", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"50.133.93.215", "uid":"2197128720", "session_id":"448237465", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484442123", "session_id":"448237465"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New Baltimore, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.6757", "longitude":"-82.7773", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448237465"},
          { "time":"1484438654", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 4:04pm", "time_total":"615", "ip_address":"107.77.214.189", "uid":"591320346", "session_id":"448176177", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484438654", "session_id":"448176177"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://tennisnow.com/Blogs/NET-POSTS/January-2017/After-Random-Mistake,%e2%80%9d-Bouchard-and-Hogstedt-on-S.aspx", "referrer_domain":"tennisnow.com", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0544", "longitude":"-118.2440", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448176177"},
          { "time":"1484437514", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 3:45pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"73.67.71.53", "uid":"1109035921", "session_id":"448154274", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484437514", "session_id":"448154274"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 8.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Davenport, Florida, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"28.1911", "longitude":"-81.6068", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448154274"},
          { "time":"1484437343", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 3:42pm", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"174.228.136.243", "uid":"4078069682", "session_id":"448150948", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484437343", "session_id":"448150948"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=448150948"},
          { "time":"1484429197", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 1:26pm", "time_total":"431", "ip_address":"50.176.65.87", "uid":"2164769789", "session_id":"447983209", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484429197", "session_id":"447983209"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Boston, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.3159", "longitude":"-71.0559", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447983209"},
          { "time":"1484429073", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 1:24pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"45.55.229.93", "uid":"2989184430", "session_id":"447980537", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484429073", "session_id":"447980537"}, "landing_page":"http://customerstories.net/", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 34.0", "operating_system":"Windows 8.1", "screen_resolution":"1024x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7421", "longitude":"-74.0018", "organization":"Digital Ocean", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447980537"},
          { "time":"1484428905", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 1:21pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"173.80.9.110", "uid":"273811093", "session_id":"447976915", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484428905", "session_id":"447976915"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Beckley, West Virginia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.8164", "longitude":"-81.2329", "hostname":"suddenlink.net", "organization":"Suddenlink Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447976915"},
          { "time":"1484427067", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 12:51pm", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"174.255.205.60", "uid":"4181663290", "session_id":"447937115", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484337710", "session_id":"446307348"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447937115"},
          { "time":"1484426682", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 12:44pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.213.5.241", "uid":"271654536", "session_id":"447928477", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484403892", "session_id":"447422325"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Hayward, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.6745", "longitude":"-122.0883", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447928477"},
          { "time":"1484426397", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 12:39pm", "time_total":"316", "ip_address":"108.83.185.221", "uid":"2988850369", "session_id":"447922243", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484426397", "session_id":"447922243"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Sacramento, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.5137", "longitude":"-121.4979", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447922243"},
          { "time":"1484422761", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 11:39am", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"46.99.77.86", "uid":"4053066141", "session_id":"447842246", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"14", "first_visit": {"time":"1484151392", "session_id":"442121009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Albania", "country_code":"al", "latitude":"41.0000", "longitude":"20.0000", "organization":"Ipko Telecommunications Llc", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447842246"},
          { "time":"1484421581", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 11:19am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"50.173.9.26", "uid":"3682399824", "session_id":"447815552", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484421581", "session_id":"447815552"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Yuba City, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.0529", "longitude":"-121.7329", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447815552"},
          { "time":"1484420856", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 11:07am", "time_total":"253", "ip_address":"46.99.36.22", "uid":"4053066141", "session_id":"447799476", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"14", "first_visit": {"time":"1484151392", "session_id":"442121009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Albania", "country_code":"al", "latitude":"41.0000", "longitude":"20.0000", "organization":"Ipko Telecommunications Llc", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447799476"},
          { "time":"1484420831", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 11:07am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"66.60.218.34", "uid":"4223809398", "session_id":"447798962", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484420831", "session_id":"447798962"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New Ulm, Minnesota, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"44.3041", "longitude":"-94.4356", "hostname":"newulmtel.net", "organization":"Nu-telecom", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447798962"},
          { "time":"1484419483", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 10:44am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.36.232.20", "uid":"3683177040", "session_id":"447768786", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484419483", "session_id":"447768786"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 8.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Ukiah, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.1266", "longitude":"-123.2805", "hostname":"fusionbroadband.com", "organization":"Sonic.net", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447768786"},
          { "time":"1484418168", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 10:22am", "time_total":"604", "ip_address":"162.207.179.9", "uid":"1152059504", "session_id":"447738573", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484412723", "session_id":"447611883"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 28.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Birmingham, Alabama, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.6059", "longitude":"-86.7589", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447738573"},
          { "time":"1484417981", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 10:19am", "time_total":"35", "ip_address":"216.4.56.183", "uid":"2385899689", "session_id":"447734134", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484417981", "session_id":"447734134"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "organization":"Jasper Technologies", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447734134"},
          { "time":"1484417663", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 10:14am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"108.8.114.60", "uid":"2609590684", "session_id":"447726640", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484417663", "session_id":"447726640"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Frackville, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7852", "longitude":"-76.2230", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Internet Services", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447726640"},
          { "time":"1484417033", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 10:03am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"173.31.208.133", "uid":"2287316940", "session_id":"447712048", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484417033", "session_id":"447712048"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Mound, Minnesota, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"44.9347", "longitude":"-93.6762", "hostname":"mchsi.com", "organization":"Mediacom Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447712048"},
          { "time":"1484414870", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 9:27am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"69.137.114.188", "uid":"306372492", "session_id":"447661492", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484414870", "session_id":"447661492"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Franklin, Tennessee, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.9086", "longitude":"-86.7811", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447661492"},
          { "time":"1484414687", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 9:24am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.2.93.171", "uid":"851121522", "session_id":"447657249", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484414687", "session_id":"447657249"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Saskatoon, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"52.1526", "longitude":"-106.7066", "hostname":"shawcable.net", "organization":"Shaw Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447657249"},
          { "time":"1484414431", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 9:20am", "time_total":"585", "ip_address":"75.167.228.62", "uid":"4138376824", "session_id":"447651127", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484414431", "session_id":"447651127"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Davenport, Iowa, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.5798", "longitude":"-90.6250", "hostname":"qwest.net", "organization":"Centurylink", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447651127"},
          { "time":"1484414272", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 9:17am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.226.81", "uid":"1593706218", "session_id":"447647322", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484414272", "session_id":"447647322"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8132", "longitude":"-73.9386", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447647322"},
          { "time":"1484414095", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 9:14am", "time_total":"123", "ip_address":"172.58.200.20", "uid":"236926475", "session_id":"447643108", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484404864", "session_id":"447443283"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.9523", "longitude":"-75.1638", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447643108"},
          { "time":"1484413188", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:59am", "time_total":"243", "ip_address":"46.99.130.182", "uid":"4053066141", "session_id":"447622533", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"14", "first_visit": {"time":"1484151392", "session_id":"442121009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Albania", "country_code":"al", "latitude":"41.0000", "longitude":"20.0000", "organization":"Ipko Telecommunications Llc", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447622533"},
          { "time":"1484412972", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:56am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"184.147.183.175", "uid":"1631931252", "session_id":"447617618", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484412972", "session_id":"447617618"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Elmira, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"43.5996", "longitude":"-80.5604", "hostname":"bell.ca", "organization":"Bell Canada", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447617618"},
          { "time":"1484412781", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:53am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"24.220.252.15", "uid":"2385999974", "session_id":"447613250", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484412781", "session_id":"447613250"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New Rockford, North Dakota, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"47.6786", "longitude":"-99.0801", "hostname":"midco.net", "organization":"Midcontinent Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447613250"},
          { "time":"1484412780", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:53am", "time_total":"158", "ip_address":"73.106.77.0", "uid":"3199182268", "session_id":"447613218", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484412780", "session_id":"447613218"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Atlanta, Georgia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.7242", "longitude":"-84.4683", "organization":"Xfinity Wifi", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447613218"},
          { "time":"1484412723", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:52am", "time_total":"540", "ip_address":"162.207.179.9", "uid":"1152059504", "session_id":"447611883", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484412723", "session_id":"447611883"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 28.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Birmingham, Alabama, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.6059", "longitude":"-86.7589", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447611883"},
          { "time":"1484412641", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:50am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"75.190.197.113", "uid":"1507509818", "session_id":"447609928", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484412641", "session_id":"447609928"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Huntersville, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.4034", "longitude":"-80.8611", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447609928"},
          { "time":"1484412329", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:45am", "time_total":"412", "ip_address":"70.195.132.66", "uid":"100183702", "session_id":"447602884", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484317622", "session_id":"445724413"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Alden, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.9038", "longitude":"-78.5008", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447602884"},
          { "time":"1484412130", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:42am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"73.217.231.148", "uid":"721709109", "session_id":"447598501", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484412130", "session_id":"447598501"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Blue Springs, Missouri, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.0050", "longitude":"-94.2499", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447598501"},
          { "time":"1484411926", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:38am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"76.69.251.86", "uid":"2116516148", "session_id":"447593807", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484411926", "session_id":"447593807"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Montr√©al, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"45.4546", "longitude":"-73.5985", "hostname":"bell.ca", "organization":"Bell Canada", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447593807"},
          { "time":"1484411533", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:32am", "time_total":"63", "ip_address":"73.88.220.214", "uid":"2635497603", "session_id":"447584977", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484411533", "session_id":"447584977"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Franklin, Indiana, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.4835", "longitude":"-86.0478", "organization":"Xfinity Wifi", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447584977"},
          { "time":"1484411297", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:28am", "time_total":"601", "ip_address":"73.44.159.214", "uid":"2534324565", "session_id":"447579432", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484409525", "session_id":"447539525"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Opera 29.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.0076", "longitude":"-87.6956", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447579432"},
          { "time":"1484410627", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:17am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"24.239.113.98", "session_id":"447564463", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484410627", "session_id":"447564463"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Youngstown, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.0246", "longitude":"-80.6697", "hostname":"zoominternet.net", "organization":"Armstrong Cable Services", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447564463"},
          { "time":"1484410463", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:14am", "time_total":"320", "ip_address":"71.203.115.52", "uid":"4240238811", "session_id":"447560723", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484407026", "session_id":"447489628"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 34.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x598", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Bear, Delaware, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.6025", "longitude":"-75.6945", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447560723"},
          { "time":"1484410445", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:14am", "time_total":"31", "ip_address":"107.77.218.86", "uid":"3472592808", "session_id":"447560334", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484410445", "session_id":"447560334"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Universal City, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"29.5423", "longitude":"-98.2964", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447560334"},
          { "time":"1484410316", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:11am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"66.8.170.79", "uid":"2699513601", "session_id":"447557316", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484410316", "session_id":"447557316"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"414x736", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Kula, Hawaii, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"20.7020", "longitude":"-156.2581", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447557316"},
          { "time":"1484410244", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:10am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"69.146.177.71", "uid":"3228075699", "session_id":"447555738", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484410244", "session_id":"447555738"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 8.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"La Junta, Colorado, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.8463", "longitude":"-103.5836", "hostname":"bresnan.net", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447555738"},
          { "time":"1484409719", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8:01am", "time_total":"360", "ip_address":"98.160.185.101", "uid":"1059231152", "session_id":"447543838", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484409719", "session_id":"447543838"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"North Las Vegas, Nevada, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.2729", "longitude":"-115.1333", "hostname":"cox.net", "organization":"Cox Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447543838"},
          { "time":"1484409612", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 8am", "time_total":"30", "ip_address":"69.136.134.136", "uid":"2903286732", "session_id":"447541275", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484409612", "session_id":"447541275"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 34.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Warren, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.5144", "longitude":"-83.0159", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Xfinity Wifi", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447541275"},
          { "time":"1484409525", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 7:58am", "time_total":"885", "ip_address":"73.44.159.214", "uid":"2534324565", "session_id":"447539525", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484409525", "session_id":"447539525"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Opera 29.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.0076", "longitude":"-87.6956", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447539525"},
          { "time":"1484408675", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 7:44am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.222.37", "uid":"2414330324", "session_id":"447522969", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484408675", "session_id":"447522969"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.7787", "longitude":"-96.8217", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447522969"},
          { "time":"1484408153", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 7:35am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.198.198.60", "uid":"1279396116", "session_id":"447512487", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484408153", "session_id":"447512487"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.4734", "longitude":"-79.9903", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447512487"},
          { "time":"1484407026", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 7:17am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"71.203.115.52", "uid":"4240238811", "session_id":"447489628", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484407026", "session_id":"447489628"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 34.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x598", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Bear, Delaware, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.6025", "longitude":"-75.6945", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447489628"},
          { "time":"1484406985", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 7:16am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"66.87.77.128", "uid":"2725752390", "session_id":"447488813", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484406985", "session_id":"447488813"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.9223", "longitude":"-87.7555", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447488813"},
          { "time":"1484406925", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 7:15am", "time_total":"600", "ip_address":"68.224.85.236", "uid":"183603932", "session_id":"447487584", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484406925", "session_id":"447487584"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Las Vegas, Nevada, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.1113", "longitude":"-115.2791", "hostname":"cox.net", "organization":"Cox Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447487584"},
          { "time":"1484406742", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 7:12am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"184.17.239.12", "uid":"4254464705", "session_id":"447483985", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484406742", "session_id":"447483985"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Fort Wayne, Indiana, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.0394", "longitude":"-85.2322", "hostname":"frontiernet.net", "organization":"Frontier Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447483985"},
          { "time":"1484406405", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 7:06am", "time_total":"61", "ip_address":"71.178.185.65", "uid":"3049034289", "session_id":"447477294", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484406405", "session_id":"447477294"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Rockville, Maryland, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.1074", "longitude":"-77.0997", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Fios", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447477294"},
          { "time":"1484405800", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:56am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"108.211.47.201", "uid":"2695710141", "session_id":"447463999", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484402455", "session_id":"447391995"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Merced, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.4115", "longitude":"-120.5039", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447463999"},
          { "time":"1484405660", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:54am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"75.167.161.105", "uid":"2494545339", "session_id":"447460803", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484405660", "session_id":"447460803"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Meridian, Idaho, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"43.5992", "longitude":"-116.4234", "hostname":"qwest.net", "organization":"Centurylink", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447460803"},
          { "time":"1484405614", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:53am", "time_total":"121", "ip_address":"172.58.224.230", "uid":"3262280283", "session_id":"447459744", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484405614", "session_id":"447459744"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Brooklyn, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7035", "longitude":"-73.9182", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447459744"},
          { "time":"1484405461", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:51am", "time_total":"111", "ip_address":"31.218.49.50", "uid":"3037775369", "session_id":"447456260", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484405461", "session_id":"447456260"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 37.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"720x1184", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Abu Dhabi, The United Arab Emirates", "country_code":"ae", "latitude":"24.4667", "longitude":"54.3667", "organization":"Emirates Telecommunications Corporation", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447456260"},
          { "time":"1484405341", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:49am", "time_total":"121", "ip_address":"74.66.229.3", "uid":"4262962421", "session_id":"447453666", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484405341", "session_id":"447453666"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"1280x800", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Mount Vernon, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.9083", "longitude":"-73.8346", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447453666"},
          { "time":"1484404864", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:41am", "time_total":"60", "ip_address":"172.58.201.163", "uid":"236926475", "session_id":"447443283", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484404864", "session_id":"447443283"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Cleveland, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.4995", "longitude":"-81.6954", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447443283"},
          { "time":"1484404776", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:39am", "time_total":"107", "ip_address":"172.58.107.10", "uid":"3102489665", "session_id":"447441413", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484404776", "session_id":"447441413"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Grand Prairie, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.7781", "longitude":"-96.9555", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447441413"},
          { "time":"1484404511", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:35am", "time_total":"179", "ip_address":"91.187.98.121", "uid":"4053066141", "session_id":"447435723", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"14", "first_visit": {"time":"1484151392", "session_id":"442121009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Albania", "country_code":"al", "latitude":"41.0000", "longitude":"20.0000", "organization":"Ipko Telecommunications Llc", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447435723"},
          { "time":"1484404145", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:29am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"49.34.242.48", "uid":"532824431", "session_id":"447427783", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"11", "first_visit": {"time":"1484319949", "session_id":"445796301"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Latipur, India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"22.6167", "longitude":"70.5333", "organization":"Reliance Jio Infocomm Ltd", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447427783"},
          { "time":"1484403892", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:24am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.213.12.85", "uid":"271654536", "session_id":"447422325", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484403892", "session_id":"447422325"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0544", "longitude":"-118.2440", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447422325"},
          { "time":"1484403403", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:16am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"99.8.179.35", "uid":"2279658536", "session_id":"447412126", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484403403", "session_id":"447412126"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Mesquite, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.8195", "longitude":"-96.6338", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447412126"},
          { "time":"1484403393", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:16am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.26.229.149", "uid":"3295298336", "session_id":"447411899", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484403393", "session_id":"447411899"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Scottsdale, Arizona, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.4656", "longitude":"-111.9253", "hostname":"qwest.net", "organization":"Centurylink", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447411899"},
          { "time":"1484403140", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:12am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"98.24.209.233", "uid":"2778797435", "session_id":"447406602", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484403140", "session_id":"447406602"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Fayetteville, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.1714", "longitude":"-78.8956", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447406602"},
          { "time":"1484402678", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6:04am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"173.242.210.201", "uid":"259428210", "session_id":"447396796", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484402678", "session_id":"447396796"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"French", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Caplan, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"48.0399", "longitude":"-65.6618", "hostname":"navigue.com", "organization":"Navigue.com", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447396796"},
          { "time":"1484402455", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 6am", "time_total":"913", "ip_address":"108.211.47.201", "uid":"2695710141", "session_id":"447391995", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484402455", "session_id":"447391995"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Merced, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.4115", "longitude":"-120.5039", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447391995"},
          { "time":"1484401259", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 5:40am", "time_total":"71", "ip_address":"5.102.254.139", "uid":"2722712030", "session_id":"447367723", "actions":"3", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484401259", "session_id":"447367723"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1280x800", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"https://varmour.com/partners", "referrer_domain":"varmour.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Tel Aviv, Israel", "country_code":"il", "latitude":"32.0667", "longitude":"34.7667", "hostname":"018.net.il", "organization":"Xfone", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447367723"},
          { "time":"1484400114", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 5:21am", "time_total":"817", "ip_address":"91.187.98.121", "uid":"4053066141", "session_id":"447344351", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"14", "first_visit": {"time":"1484151392", "session_id":"442121009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Albania", "country_code":"al", "latitude":"41.0000", "longitude":"20.0000", "organization":"Ipko Telecommunications Llc", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447344351"},
          { "time":"1484399847", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 5:17am", "time_total":"61", "ip_address":"208.54.44.161", "uid":"427907614", "session_id":"447339497", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484153515", "session_id":"442175280"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0", "operating_system":"Linux", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.7490", "longitude":"-84.3880", "hostname":"tmodns.net", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447339497"},
          { "time":"1484398432", "time_pretty":"Sat Jan 14 2017, 4:53am", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"91.187.98.121", "uid":"4053066141", "session_id":"447313654", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"14", "first_visit": {"time":"1484151392", "session_id":"442121009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Albania", "country_code":"al", "latitude":"41.0000", "longitude":"20.0000", "organization":"Ipko Telecommunications Llc", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=447313654"},
          { "time":"1484375281", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 10:28pm", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"49.34.96.88", "uid":"532824431", "session_id":"446980831", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"11", "first_visit": {"time":"1484319949", "session_id":"445796301"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"23.0333", "longitude":"72.6167", "organization":"Reliance Jio Infocomm Ltd", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446980831"},
          { "time":"1484374335", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 10:12pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"50.138.145.80", "uid":"1465975788", "session_id":"446968384", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484231285", "session_id":"443763275"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Waterbury, Connecticut, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.5515", "longitude":"-72.9927", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446968384"},
          { "time":"1484373317", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 9:55pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"49.34.96.88", "uid":"532824431", "session_id":"446955182", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"11", "first_visit": {"time":"1484319949", "session_id":"445796301"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"23.0333", "longitude":"72.6167", "organization":"Reliance Jio Infocomm Ltd", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446955182"},
          { "time":"1484370812", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 9:13pm", "time_total":"119", "ip_address":"183.171.24.91", "uid":"3464330260", "session_id":"446920803", "actions":"3", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484370812", "session_id":"446920803"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"https://varmour.com/partners", "referrer_domain":"varmour.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Petaling Jaya, Malaysia", "country_code":"my", "latitude":"3.1070", "longitude":"101.6305", "organization":"Celcom Internet Service Provider", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446920803"},
          { "time":"1484369967", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 8:59pm", "time_total":"214", "ip_address":"24.91.223.121", "uid":"605855059", "session_id":"446909944", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"9", "first_visit": {"time":"1482514748", "session_id":"411204811"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://officechai.com/news/elon-musk-receives-product-suggestion-twitter-tesla-implements-6-days-later/", "referrer_domain":"officechai.com", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Rehoboth, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8428", "longitude":"-71.2455", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446909944"},
          { "time":"1484359612", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 6:06pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"97.102.135.215", "uid":"269956251", "session_id":"446756408", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484321072", "session_id":"445830170"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Kissimmee, Florida, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"28.3120", "longitude":"-81.5890", "hostname":"bhn.net", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446756408"},
          { "time":"1484358679", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 5:51pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"185.173.207.67", "uid":"2955941882", "session_id":"446743478", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484320012", "session_id":"445798133"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Linux", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446743478"},
          { "time":"1484357376", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 5:29pm", "time_total":"121", "ip_address":"172.58.12.76", "uid":"1669657674", "session_id":"446723276", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1483974519", "session_id":"438034604"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x534", "javascript":"1", "language":"Spanish", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.4484", "longitude":"-112.0740", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446723276"},
          { "time":"1484356362", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 5:12pm", "time_total":"1794", "ip_address":"96.95.217.238", "uid":"1258059098", "session_id":"446706488", "actions":"23", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484174399", "session_id":"442678410"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1440x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"https://varmour.com/", "referrer_domain":"varmour.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Menlo Park, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.4590", "longitude":"-122.1781", "hostname":"comcastbusiness.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446706488"},
          { "time":"1484354407", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 4:40pm", "time_total":"141", "ip_address":"185.173.207.76", "uid":"2955941882", "session_id":"446672417", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484320012", "session_id":"445798133"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446672417"},
          { "time":"1484353533", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 4:25pm", "time_total":"348", "ip_address":"46.99.86.226", "uid":"4053066141", "session_id":"446657086", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"14", "first_visit": {"time":"1484151392", "session_id":"442121009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Albania", "country_code":"al", "latitude":"41.0000", "longitude":"20.0000", "organization":"Ipko Telecommunications Llc", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446657086"},
          { "time":"1484350449", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 3:34pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"108.36.100.232", "uid":"12643883", "session_id":"446601418", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484347357", "session_id":"446540115"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Sellersville, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.3611", "longitude":"-75.3201", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Fios", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446601418"},
          { "time":"1484350302", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 3:31pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.226.183", "uid":"1030176296", "session_id":"446598829", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1483897135", "session_id":"436456067"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8132", "longitude":"-73.9386", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446598829"},
          { "time":"1484349921", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 3:25pm", "time_total":"247", "ip_address":"107.77.216.111", "uid":"2367507992", "session_id":"446591608", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484317584", "session_id":"445723450"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"28.0222", "longitude":"-81.7329", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446591608"},
          { "time":"1484349714", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 3:21pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"162.40.59.141", "uid":"3306032365", "session_id":"446587797", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484349714", "session_id":"446587797"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Harrison, Arkansas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.2298", "longitude":"-93.1077", "hostname":"windstream.net", "organization":"Windstream Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446587797"},
          { "time":"1484347357", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 2:42pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"108.36.100.232", "uid":"12643883", "session_id":"446540115", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484347357", "session_id":"446540115"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Sellersville, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.3611", "longitude":"-75.3201", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Fios", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446540115"},
          { "time":"1484345542", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 2:12pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"204.100.182.191", "uid":"3188593010", "session_id":"446499044", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484345542", "session_id":"446499044"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Murrieta, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.5789", "longitude":"-117.1412", "organization":"Riverside County Office Of Education", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446499044"},
          { "time":"1484342794", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 1:26pm", "time_total":"20", "ip_address":"148.75.194.42", "uid":"2622588926", "session_id":"446434658", "actions":"3", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484342794", "session_id":"446434658"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1440x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://googleads.g.doubleclick.net/", "referrer_domain":"googleads.g.doubleclick.net", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Smithtown, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8594", "longitude":"-73.2121", "hostname":"optonline.net", "organization":"Optimum Online", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446434658"},
          { "time":"1484342667", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 1:24pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.36.232.20", "uid":"3081619716", "session_id":"446431603", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484342667", "session_id":"446431603"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 8.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Ukiah, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.1266", "longitude":"-123.2805", "hostname":"fusionbroadband.com", "organization":"Sonic.net", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446431603"},
          { "time":"1484341811", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 1:10pm", "time_total":"30", "ip_address":"24.4.17.246", "uid":"2359328047", "session_id":"446410685", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484341811", "session_id":"446410685"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/hubspot/summit/finding-inspiration-and-smart-peers-at-the-summit", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Windows 10", "screen_resolution":"1280x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com/", "referrer_domain":"2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Pleasanton, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.6624", "longitude":"-121.8747", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446410685"},
          { "time":"1484339603", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 12:33pm", "time_total":"605", "ip_address":"50.143.129.107", "uid":"2953643240", "session_id":"446354188", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1483986993", "session_id":"438425220"}, "landing_page":"https://trunity.customerstories.net/umass-lowell/form-and-function-of-living-things-shea/umass-lowell-department-of-biology", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1280x800", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"https://linkedin.com/", "referrer_domain":"linkedin.com", "referrer_type":"social media", "geolocation":"San Rafael, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.9719", "longitude":"-122.5023", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446354188"},
          { "time":"1484337710", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 12:01pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.255.205.60", "uid":"4181663290", "session_id":"446307348", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484337710", "session_id":"446307348"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446307348"},
          { "time":"1484335877", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 11:31am", "time_total":"479", "ip_address":"96.50.249.57", "uid":"341821017", "session_id":"446262000", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484335877", "session_id":"446262000"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Vernon, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"50.2604", "longitude":"-119.2774", "hostname":"shawcable.net", "organization":"Shaw Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446262000"},
          { "time":"1484335473", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 11:24am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"74.199.34.87", "uid":"604920910", "session_id":"446251783", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484335473", "session_id":"446251783"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"414x736", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Mason, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.5797", "longitude":"-84.4603", "hostname":"wideopenwest.com", "organization":"Wideopenwest", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446251783"},
          { "time":"1484335401", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 11:23am", "time_total":"1722", "ip_address":"74.102.208.92", "uid":"2730617496", "session_id":"446250004", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484335401", "session_id":"446250004"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Windows 7", "screen_resolution":"1440x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://googleads.g.doubleclick.net/", "referrer_domain":"googleads.g.doubleclick.net", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Cranford, New Jersey, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6559", "longitude":"-74.3045", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Fios", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446250004"},
          { "time":"1484334441", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 11:07am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"70.174.106.28", "uid":"948808196", "session_id":"446225204", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484334441", "session_id":"446225204"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Newport News, Virginia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.1170", "longitude":"-76.5135", "hostname":"cox.net", "organization":"Cox Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446225204"},
          { "time":"1484331502", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 10:18am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.214.109.176", "uid":"201482449", "session_id":"446145799", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484331502", "session_id":"446145799"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Brooklyn, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7035", "longitude":"-73.9182", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446145799"},
          { "time":"1484330335", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 9:58am", "time_total":"264", "ip_address":"172.56.20.224", "uid":"3170774326", "session_id":"446113626", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"8", "first_visit": {"time":"1483972693", "session_id":"437978387"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.5207", "longitude":"-86.8025", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446113626"},
          { "time":"1484329683", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 9:48am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"24.44.243.101", "uid":"465183207", "session_id":"446094387", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484329683", "session_id":"446094387"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Milford, Connecticut, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.2241", "longitude":"-73.0517", "hostname":"optonline.net", "organization":"Optimum Online", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446094387"},
          { "time":"1484328635", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 9:30am", "time_total":"398", "ip_address":"46.99.44.74", "uid":"4053066141", "session_id":"446063306", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"14", "first_visit": {"time":"1484151392", "session_id":"442121009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Albania", "country_code":"al", "latitude":"41.0000", "longitude":"20.0000", "organization":"Ipko Telecommunications Llc", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446063306"},
          { "time":"1484327546", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 9:12am", "time_total":"258", "ip_address":"39.36.252.167", "uid":"336158221", "session_id":"446030569", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484316179", "session_id":"445682774"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x534", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Faisalabad, Pakistan", "country_code":"pk", "latitude":"31.4167", "longitude":"73.0833", "organization":"Ptcl", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=446030569"},
          { "time":"1484326114", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 8:48am", "time_total":"239", "ip_address":"128.177.161.182", "uid":"4173550192", "session_id":"445985528", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1483972012", "session_id":"437957115"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"Spanish", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"San Jose, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.3874", "longitude":"-121.9024", "organization":"Jasper Technologies", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445985528"},
          { "time":"1484325101", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 8:31am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"163.11.44.121", "uid":"1810095652", "session_id":"445953833", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484325101", "session_id":"445953833"}, "landing_page":"https://trunity.customerstories.net/life-on-this-rock/life-on-this-rock-shea/introduction-to-biology-for-students-majoring-in-other-fields", "web_browser":"Safari 9.1", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1440x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://google.com/search?q=%5Bsecure+search%5D", "referrer_domain":"google.com", "referrer_search":"[secure search]", "referrer_type":"search", "geolocation":"Cedarville, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.7444", "longitude":"-83.7669", "organization":"Oarnet", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445953833"},
          { "time":"1484325034", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 8:30am", "time_total":"696", "ip_address":"172.56.20.224", "uid":"3170774326", "session_id":"445951680", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"8", "first_visit": {"time":"1483972693", "session_id":"437978387"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.5207", "longitude":"-86.8025", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445951680"},
          { "time":"1484324702", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 8:25am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"70.195.135.3", "uid":"1917721958", "session_id":"445941751", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484324702", "session_id":"445941751"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Rochester, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"43.1518", "longitude":"-77.5852", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445941751"},
          { "time":"1484324571", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 8:22am", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"172.56.15.153", "uid":"3731561108", "session_id":"445937781", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484324571", "session_id":"445937781"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Houston, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"29.7633", "longitude":"-95.3633", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445937781"},
          { "time":"1484324551", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 8:22am", "time_total":"297", "ip_address":"70.192.66.48", "uid":"2511382229", "session_id":"445937199", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484324551", "session_id":"445937199"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Madison, New Jersey, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7598", "longitude":"-74.4171", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445937199"},
          { "time":"1484323970", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 8:12am", "time_total":"240", "ip_address":"67.237.206.137", "uid":"2206527633", "session_id":"445919495", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484323970", "session_id":"445919495"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 43.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Jonesborough, Tennessee, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.3022", "longitude":"-82.4825", "hostname":"embarqhsd.net", "organization":"Centurylink", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445919495"},
          { "time":"1484323818", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 8:10am", "time_total":"25", "ip_address":"185.173.207.76", "uid":"2955941882", "session_id":"445914920", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484320012", "session_id":"445798133"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445914920"},
          { "time":"1484323406", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 8:03am", "time_total":"440", "ip_address":"23.25.179.125", "uid":"2367507992", "session_id":"445902502", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484317584", "session_id":"445723450"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Mobile, Alabama, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"30.6944", "longitude":"-88.0430", "hostname":"comcastbusiness.net", "organization":"Comcast Business Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445902502"},
          { "time":"1484323096", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:58am", "time_total":"240", "ip_address":"174.255.204.231", "uid":"3760032937", "session_id":"445892750", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484323096", "session_id":"445892750"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x534", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445892750"},
          { "time":"1484322851", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:54am", "time_total":"60", "ip_address":"144.230.63.36", "uid":"3560946931", "session_id":"445885265", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484322851", "session_id":"445885265"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Internet Explorer 11.0", "operating_system":"Windows 7", "screen_resolution":"1242x698", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Leawood, Kansas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.9586", "longitude":"-94.6202", "organization":"Sprint, Business Serices Group", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445885265"},
          { "time":"1484321751", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:35am", "time_total":"403", "ip_address":"66.87.132.181", "uid":"1548057562", "session_id":"445851100", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484321751", "session_id":"445851100"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Asheboro, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.7382", "longitude":"-79.7690", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445851100"},
          { "time":"1484321566", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:32am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"172.56.31.7", "uid":"2609988862", "session_id":"445845308", "actions":"4", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484321566", "session_id":"445845308"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x534", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Los Angeles, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0522", "longitude":"-118.2437", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445845308"},
          { "time":"1484321519", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:31am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"172.56.31.7", "uid":"850286854", "session_id":"445843710", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484321519", "session_id":"445843710"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x534", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Los Angeles, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0522", "longitude":"-118.2437", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445843710"},
          { "time":"1484321458", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:30am", "time_total":"121", "ip_address":"107.77.209.86", "uid":"923488412", "session_id":"445841825", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484321458", "session_id":"445841825"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8500", "longitude":"-87.6500", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445841825"},
          { "time":"1484321408", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:30am", "time_total":"110", "ip_address":"173.46.77.165", "uid":"3591167379", "session_id":"445840242", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484321408", "session_id":"445840242"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Louisville, Colorado, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.9558", "longitude":"-105.1683", "hostname":"updated.as8218.us", "organization":"Jasper Technologies", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445840242"},
          { "time":"1484321257", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:27am", "time_total":"233", "ip_address":"107.185.15.156", "uid":"1747747150", "session_id":"445835778", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484321257", "session_id":"445835778"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 51.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Santa Paula, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.4014", "longitude":"-119.0753", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445835778"},
          { "time":"1484321072", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:24am", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"97.102.135.215", "uid":"269956251", "session_id":"445830170", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484321072", "session_id":"445830170"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Kissimmee, Florida, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"28.3120", "longitude":"-81.5890", "hostname":"bhn.net", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445830170"},
          { "time":"1484320985", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:23am", "time_total":"244", "ip_address":"172.58.46.167", "uid":"718314114", "session_id":"445827449", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484320985", "session_id":"445827449"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Seattle, Washington, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"47.3824", "longitude":"-122.3138", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445827449"},
          { "time":"1484320293", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:11am", "time_total":"193", "ip_address":"107.77.211.143", "uid":"2250071051", "session_id":"445806416", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484320293", "session_id":"445806416"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 28.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0544", "longitude":"-118.2440", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445806416"},
          { "time":"1484320289", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:11am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"76.234.46.26", "uid":"1260517387", "session_id":"445806288", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484320289", "session_id":"445806288"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Crystal Lake, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.2343", "longitude":"-88.3068", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445806288"},
          { "time":"1484320232", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:10am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.0.112.124", "uid":"1596977851", "session_id":"445804477", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484320232", "session_id":"445804477"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Calgary, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"51.0412", "longitude":"-114.0762", "hostname":"shawcable.net", "organization":"Shaw Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445804477"},
          { "time":"1484320012", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:06am", "time_total":"240", "ip_address":"185.173.207.78", "uid":"2955941882", "session_id":"445798133", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484320012", "session_id":"445798133"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445798133"},
          { "time":"1484319949", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:05am", "time_total":"230", "ip_address":"49.34.153.176", "uid":"532824431", "session_id":"445796301", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"11", "first_visit": {"time":"1484319949", "session_id":"445796301"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Ahmedabad, India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"23.0333", "longitude":"72.6167", "organization":"Reliance Jio Infocomm Ltd", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445796301"},
          { "time":"1484319879", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:04am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"45.36.194.234", "uid":"321937342", "session_id":"445794342", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484270292", "session_id":"444853883"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Yadkinville, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.1242", "longitude":"-80.6351", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445794342"},
          { "time":"1484319813", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:03am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"96.21.4.58", "uid":"3816212733", "session_id":"445792179", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484319813", "session_id":"445792179"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Vaudreuil-dorion, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"45.4000", "longitude":"-74.0333", "hostname":"videotron.ca", "organization":"Videotron Ltee", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445792179"},
          { "time":"1484319774", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:02am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"65.27.190.138", "uid":"798207273", "session_id":"445791005", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484319774", "session_id":"445791005"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Cincinnati, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.1732", "longitude":"-84.6584", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445791005"},
          { "time":"1484319676", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 7:01am", "time_total":"605", "ip_address":"216.10.232.20", "uid":"2839882742", "session_id":"445787840", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"16", "first_visit": {"time":"1480450383", "session_id":"380216613"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/vocera/summit/value-received-broadening-customer-advocacy-experience", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Windows 10", "screen_resolution":"1366x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com/", "referrer_domain":"2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Harrow, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"42.0363", "longitude":"-82.9182", "organization":"G1 Hispeed", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445787840"},
          { "time":"1484319039", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 6:50am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"172.56.20.224", "uid":"3170774326", "session_id":"445767942", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"8", "first_visit": {"time":"1483972693", "session_id":"437978387"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.5207", "longitude":"-86.8025", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445767942"},
          { "time":"1484317802", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 6:30am", "time_total":"152", "ip_address":"97.82.70.119", "uid":"4276121939", "session_id":"445729997", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484317802", "session_id":"445729997"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Guin, Alabama, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.9816", "longitude":"-87.8854", "hostname":"charter.com", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445729997"},
          { "time":"1484317622", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 6:27am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"172.101.181.76", "uid":"100183702", "session_id":"445724413", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484317622", "session_id":"445724413"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Rochester, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"43.1267", "longitude":"-77.7316", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445724413"},
          { "time":"1484317584", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 6:26am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"23.25.179.125", "uid":"2367507992", "session_id":"445723450", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484317584", "session_id":"445723450"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Mobile, Alabama, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"30.6944", "longitude":"-88.0430", "hostname":"comcastbusiness.net", "organization":"Comcast Business Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445723450"},
          { "time":"1484317366", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 6:22am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"162.157.219.74", "uid":"4182366473", "session_id":"445716980", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484317366", "session_id":"445716980"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Calgary, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"51.1387", "longitude":"-114.2015", "hostname":"telus.net", "organization":"Telus Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445716980"},
          { "time":"1484317239", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 6:20am", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"107.77.164.31", "uid":"3904627874", "session_id":"445713262", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484070010", "session_id":"440343195"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445713262"},
          { "time":"1484316179", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 6:02am", "time_total":"311", "ip_address":"43.245.11.161", "uid":"336158221", "session_id":"445682774", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484316179", "session_id":"445682774"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x534", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Pakistan", "country_code":"pk", "latitude":"30.0000", "longitude":"70.0000", "organization":"Ufone Gsm", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445682774"},
          { "time":"1484316027", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 6am", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"70.196.7.97", "uid":"2841366000", "session_id":"445678443", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1483372294", "session_id":"425288090"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Dallas, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.7831", "longitude":"-96.8067", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445678443"},
          { "time":"1484312940", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 5:09am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"98.223.151.147", "uid":"3124504990", "session_id":"445600492", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484230501", "session_id":"443738544"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.9759", "longitude":"-87.7016", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445600492"},
          { "time":"1484312766", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 5:06am", "time_total":"31", "ip_address":"70.208.194.62", "uid":"901333885", "session_id":"445596206", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484312766", "session_id":"445596206"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Sidney, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.2839", "longitude":"-84.1648", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445596206"},
          { "time":"1484309545", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 4:12am", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"98.223.151.147", "uid":"3124504990", "session_id":"445517694", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484230501", "session_id":"443738544"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.9759", "longitude":"-87.7016", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445517694"},
          { "time":"1484304480", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 2:48am", "time_total":"236", "ip_address":"172.56.20.224", "uid":"3170774326", "session_id":"445410253", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"8", "first_visit": {"time":"1483972693", "session_id":"437978387"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.5207", "longitude":"-86.8025", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445410253"},
          { "time":"1484298605", "time_pretty":"Fri Jan 13 2017, 1:10am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"45.55.229.234", "uid":"3310814466", "session_id":"445296783", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484298605", "session_id":"445296783"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/", "web_browser":"Safari 7.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1024x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7421", "longitude":"-74.0018", "organization":"Digital Ocean", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445296783"},
          { "time":"1484293197", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 11:39pm", "time_total":"1019", "ip_address":"172.56.20.224", "uid":"3170774326", "session_id":"445207035", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"8", "first_visit": {"time":"1483972693", "session_id":"437978387"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.5207", "longitude":"-86.8025", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445207035"},
          { "time":"1484292127", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 11:22pm", "time_total":"1076", "ip_address":"91.133.141.110", "uid":"870811435", "session_id":"445190522", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1484144517", "session_id":"441934460"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Iran", "country_code":"ir", "latitude":"35.6961", "longitude":"51.4231", "organization":"Mobinnet Wimax Expansion", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445190522"},
          { "time":"1484284687", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 9:18pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"69.64.173.132", "uid":"3930101969", "session_id":"445079673", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484284687", "session_id":"445079673"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Microsoft Edge 12 mobile", "operating_system":"Windows phone", "hardware":"Other (Windows phone)", "screen_resolution":"480x800", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Greenway Downs, Virginia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.9645", "longitude":"-77.2331", "hostname":"ilandcloud.com", "organization":"Iland Internet Solutions Corporation", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=445079673"},
          { "time":"1484278298", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 7:31pm", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"181.177.218.245", "uid":"2065311005", "session_id":"444986322", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484278298", "session_id":"444986322"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Georgetown, Guyana", "country_code":"gy", "latitude":"6.8000", "longitude":"-58.1667", "organization":"U Mobile (cellular) Inc.", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444986322"},
          { "time":"1484276842", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 7:07pm", "time_total":"60", "ip_address":"76.22.212.97", "uid":"2866541038", "session_id":"444963366", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484276842", "session_id":"444963366"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Paducah, Kentucky, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.0154", "longitude":"-88.5805", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444963366"},
          { "time":"1484274450", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 6:27pm", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"172.56.20.224", "uid":"3170774326", "session_id":"444924364", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"8", "first_visit": {"time":"1483972693", "session_id":"437978387"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.5207", "longitude":"-86.8025", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444924364"},
          { "time":"1484272214", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 5:50pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"216.10.232.20", "uid":"2839882742", "session_id":"444886686", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"16", "first_visit": {"time":"1480450383", "session_id":"380216613"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/ddn/summit/invaluable-help-with-automating-our-advocacy-data-curation", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Windows 10", "screen_resolution":"1366x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://webmail.lisalarter.com/", "referrer_domain":"webmail.lisalarter.com", "referrer_type":"email", "geolocation":"Harrow, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"42.0363", "longitude":"-82.9182", "organization":"G1 Hispeed", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444886686"},
          { "time":"1484271618", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 5:40pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"75.24.110.231", "uid":"3415883408", "session_id":"444876562", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484271618", "session_id":"444876562"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Lawrenceville, Georgia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.9350", "longitude":"-83.9538", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444876562"},
          { "time":"1484270292", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 5:18pm", "time_total":"260", "ip_address":"45.36.194.234", "uid":"321937342", "session_id":"444853883", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484270292", "session_id":"444853883"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Yadkinville, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.1242", "longitude":"-80.6351", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444853883"},
          { "time":"1484270117", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 5:15pm", "time_total":"1972", "ip_address":"172.56.41.44", "uid":"3280234542", "session_id":"444850853", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"6", "first_visit": {"time":"1484231536", "session_id":"443771348"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Las Vegas, Nevada, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.1750", "longitude":"-115.1372", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444850853"},
          { "time":"1484269531", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 5:05pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"67.45.96.85", "uid":"3085881686", "session_id":"444840501", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484269531", "session_id":"444840501"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"direcpc.com", "organization":"Hughes Network Systems", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444840501"},
          { "time":"1484268992", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 4:56pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"216.167.233.58", "uid":"1635833304", "session_id":"444831007", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1481038894", "session_id":"389789119"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/ddn/summit/invaluable-help-with-automating-our-advocacy-data-curation", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1920x1080", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com/", "referrer_domain":"2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Kirkland Lake, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"48.1446", "longitude":"-80.0377", "hostname":"eastlink.ca", "organization":"Eastlink", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444831007"},
          { "time":"1484268767", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 4:52pm", "time_total":"282", "ip_address":"172.56.18.207", "uid":"2121913468", "session_id":"444826867", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484268767", "session_id":"444826867"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"The Bronx, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8150", "longitude":"-73.9082", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444826867"},
          { "time":"1484267278", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 4:27pm", "time_total":"1521", "ip_address":"172.58.155.8", "uid":"3591625073", "session_id":"444799239", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484083763", "session_id":"440734860"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 51.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Atlanta, Georgia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.7490", "longitude":"-84.3880", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444799239"},
          { "time":"1484264398", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 3:39pm", "time_total":"371", "ip_address":"66.87.115.67", "uid":"818848088", "session_id":"444741684", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484241209", "session_id":"444080889"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Detroit, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.3314", "longitude":"-83.0457", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444741684"},
          { "time":"1484263638", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 3:27pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"24.114.64.205", "uid":"4226919679", "session_id":"444726005", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484263638", "session_id":"444726005"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Toronto, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"43.6667", "longitude":"-79.4167", "organization":"Rogers Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444726005"},
          { "time":"1484261684", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 2:54pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"73.152.112.137", "uid":"2106497414", "session_id":"444682145", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484261684", "session_id":"444682145"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Waynesboro, Virginia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.1103", "longitude":"-78.9073", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444682145"},
          { "time":"1484261243", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 2:47pm", "time_total":"240", "ip_address":"162.212.13.13", "uid":"1159775853", "session_id":"444671760", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484261243", "session_id":"444671760"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Castries, Saint Lucia", "country_code":"lc", "latitude":"14.0000", "longitude":"-61.0000", "organization":"Digicel Jamaica", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444671760"},
          { "time":"1484261006", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 2:43pm", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"91.133.141.110", "uid":"870811435", "session_id":"444665853", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1484144517", "session_id":"441934460"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Iran", "country_code":"ir", "latitude":"35.6961", "longitude":"51.4231", "organization":"Mobinnet Wimax Expansion", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444665853"},
          { "time":"1484260535", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 2:35pm", "time_total":"59", "ip_address":"71.183.46.219", "uid":"2448958088", "session_id":"444654338", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1483900969", "session_id":"436552733"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Brooklyn, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.5767", "longitude":"-73.9900", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Fios", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444654338"},
          { "time":"1484259306", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 2:15pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"66.102.8.135", "uid":"381594240", "session_id":"444623274", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484259306", "session_id":"444623274"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://google.se/search?q=%5Bsecure+search%5D", "referrer_domain":"google.se", "referrer_search":"[secure search]", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"28.0222", "longitude":"-81.7329", "hostname":"google.com", "organization":"Google", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444623274"},
          { "time":"1484258812", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 2:06pm", "time_total":"334", "ip_address":"174.255.200.126", "uid":"1582007632", "session_id":"444610931", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484258812", "session_id":"444610931"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444610931"},
          { "time":"1484258803", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 2:06pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"24.165.147.91", "uid":"1491249995", "session_id":"444610698", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484258803", "session_id":"444610698"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Erie, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.1067", "longitude":"-80.1079", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444610698"},
          { "time":"1484256741", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 1:32pm", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"76.26.242.93", "uid":"4107391202", "session_id":"444555452", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484256741", "session_id":"444555452"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Debary, Florida, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"28.8939", "longitude":"-81.3194", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444555452"},
          { "time":"1484255871", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 1:17pm", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"184.7.69.218", "uid":"3280234542", "session_id":"444531332", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"6", "first_visit": {"time":"1484231536", "session_id":"443771348"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Las Vegas, Nevada, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.1810", "longitude":"-115.1701", "hostname":"centurylinkservices.net", "organization":"Centurylink", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444531332"},
          { "time":"1484255365", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 1:09pm", "time_total":"117", "ip_address":"172.56.32.65", "uid":"2843160335", "session_id":"444517027", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484058769", "session_id":"439996276"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x480", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444517027"},
          { "time":"1484255360", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 1:09pm", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"45.74.160.201", "uid":"461773297", "session_id":"444516898", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484061601", "session_id":"440086967"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"962x601", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Ch√¢teauguay, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"45.3526", "longitude":"-73.7305", "organization":"Acn Dsl", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444516898"},
          { "time":"1484254043", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 12:47pm", "time_total":"240", "ip_address":"5.22.49.17", "uid":"3841292891", "session_id":"444480375", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484149626", "session_id":"442071666"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 47.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Iran", "country_code":"ir", "latitude":"35.6961", "longitude":"51.4231", "organization":"Asiatech Dsl Broadband Services", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444480375"},
          { "time":"1484253900", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 12:45pm", "time_total":"258", "ip_address":"174.221.2.120", "uid":"3429427743", "session_id":"444476459", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484253900", "session_id":"444476459"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.9560", "longitude":"-87.6607", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444476459"},
          { "time":"1484251095", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 11:58am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"50.26.88.144", "uid":"1772307803", "session_id":"444390802", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484251095", "session_id":"444390802"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Amarillo, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.1613", "longitude":"-101.8790", "hostname":"suddenlink.net", "organization":"Suddenlink Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444390802"},
          { "time":"1484250733", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 11:52am", "time_total":"60", "ip_address":"132.147.50.116", "session_id":"444380550", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484250733", "session_id":"444380550"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 7.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x480", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Altoona, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.5187", "longitude":"-78.3947", "hostname":"atlanticbb.net", "organization":"Atlantic Broadband", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444380550"},
          { "time":"1484248553", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 11:15am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.143.88.69", "uid":"2809567141", "session_id":"444316202", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484248553", "session_id":"444316202"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Pompano Beach, Florida, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"26.2720", "longitude":"-80.2580", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444316202"},
          { "time":"1484248466", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 11:14am", "time_total":"601", "ip_address":"66.207.221.235", "uid":"2968652126", "session_id":"444313524", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1483656620", "session_id":"431760506"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/sap/customer-case-studies/how-to-deploy-a-customer-reference-application-for-your-sales-team", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Mac OS X", "screen_resolution":"1440x900", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://google.ca/search?q=%5Bsecure+search%5D", "referrer_domain":"google.ca", "referrer_search":"[secure search]", "referrer_type":"search", "geolocation":"Toronto, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"43.6404", "longitude":"-79.3995", "hostname":"beanfield.net", "organization":"Beanfield Technologies", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444313524"},
          { "time":"1484247916", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 11:05am", "time_total":"147", "ip_address":"174.209.7.229", "uid":"3306504189", "session_id":"444296674", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"5", "first_visit": {"time":"1483493888", "session_id":"428135894"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444296674"},
          { "time":"1484247436", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 10:57am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.255.203.208", "uid":"111783689", "session_id":"444281323", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484236698", "session_id":"443938090"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444281323"},
          { "time":"1484246273", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 10:37am", "time_total":"510", "ip_address":"76.225.137.99", "uid":"2269698875", "session_id":"444244476", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484246273", "session_id":"444244476"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Granbury, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.4759", "longitude":"-97.7233", "hostname":"sbcglobal.net", "organization":"At&t U-verse", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444244476"},
          { "time":"1484245660", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 10:27am", "time_total":"590", "ip_address":"70.208.228.121", "uid":"1948293125", "session_id":"444225454", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484245660", "session_id":"444225454"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Morrow, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.3382", "longitude":"-84.1159", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444225454"},
          { "time":"1484244312", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 10:05am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.197.19", "uid":"3954838673", "session_id":"444183280", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484244312", "session_id":"444183280"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 8.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Dallas, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"32.7831", "longitude":"-96.8067", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444183280"},
          { "time":"1484243991", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 9:59am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"174.198.12.70", "uid":"3415896126", "session_id":"444169701", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484243991", "session_id":"444169701"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Milwaukee, Wisconsin, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.9967", "longitude":"-87.9879", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444169701"},
          { "time":"1484243858", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 9:57am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"47.9.230.176", "uid":"1265074640", "session_id":"444164992", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484243858", "session_id":"444164992"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Jaipur, India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"26.9167", "longitude":"75.8167", "organization":"Reliance Jio Infocomm Limited", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444164992"},
          { "time":"1484243429", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 9:50am", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"172.58.216.237", "uid":"1629029116", "session_id":"444151933", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484238244", "session_id":"443986933"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 50.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Billerica, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.5584", "longitude":"-71.2690", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444151933"},
          { "time":"1484242645", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 9:37am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"24.140.126.141", "uid":"2472576711", "session_id":"444127016", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484229947", "session_id":"443721314"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Massillon, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8182", "longitude":"-81.4918", "hostname":"sssnet.com", "organization":"Massillon Cable Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444127016"},
          { "time":"1484242595", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 9:36am", "time_total":"51", "ip_address":"184.153.184.163", "uid":"1657101761", "session_id":"444125379", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484242595", "session_id":"444125379"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 9.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Portland, Maine, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"43.6636", "longitude":"-70.3027", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444125379"},
          { "time":"1484241960", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 9:26am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"67.70.40.79", "uid":"2173923938", "session_id":"444104928", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484241960", "session_id":"444104928"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Kingston, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"44.2411", "longitude":"-76.5788", "hostname":"bell.ca", "organization":"Bell Canada", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444104928"},
          { "time":"1484241926", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 9:25am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"69.253.31.113", "uid":"2147405169", "session_id":"444103761", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484231697", "session_id":"443776433"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Wilmington, Delaware, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.8160", "longitude":"-75.5045", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444103761"},
          { "time":"1484241463", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 9:17am", "time_total":"303", "ip_address":"174.255.203.208", "uid":"111783689", "session_id":"444088660", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484236698", "session_id":"443938090"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444088660"},
          { "time":"1484241333", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 9:15am", "time_total":"233", "ip_address":"72.152.35.15", "uid":"1178902880", "session_id":"444084796", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484236699", "session_id":"443938132"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Douglasville, Georgia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.6638", "longitude":"-84.7331", "hostname":"bellsouth.net", "organization":"At&t Internet Services", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444084796"},
          { "time":"1484241209", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 9:13am", "time_total":"348", "ip_address":"66.87.115.139", "uid":"818848088", "session_id":"444080889", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484241209", "session_id":"444080889"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Detroit, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.3314", "longitude":"-83.0457", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444080889"},
          { "time":"1484240876", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 9:07am", "time_total":"119", "ip_address":"66.87.76.100", "uid":"3186447567", "session_id":"444070337", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"6", "first_visit": {"time":"1483928700", "session_id":"437127323"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.8130", "longitude":"-87.7134", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=444070337"},
          { "time":"1484238303", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 8:25am", "time_total":"14", "ip_address":"5.149.99.35", "uid":"2934620438", "session_id":"443988722", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484238303", "session_id":"443988722"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"Arabic", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Iraq", "country_code":"iq", "latitude":"33.0000", "longitude":"44.0000", "organization":"Internet Service Pool", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443988722"},
          { "time":"1484238244", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 8:24am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"172.58.216.237", "uid":"1629029116", "session_id":"443986933", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484238244", "session_id":"443986933"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 50.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Billerica, Massachusetts, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"42.5584", "longitude":"-71.2690", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443986933"},
          { "time":"1484238152", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 8:22am", "time_total":"645", "ip_address":"76.124.215.193", "uid":"3069152762", "session_id":"443983998", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484238152", "session_id":"443983998"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Boyertown, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.3468", "longitude":"-75.6809", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443983998"},
          { "time":"1484237831", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 8:17am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"99.233.114.242", "uid":"2176712855", "session_id":"443973702", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484237831", "session_id":"443973702"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Toronto, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"43.6605", "longitude":"-79.4633", "hostname":"rogers.com", "organization":"Rogers Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443973702"},
          { "time":"1484237786", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 8:16am", "time_total":"259", "ip_address":"70.208.204.122", "uid":"417808573", "session_id":"443972139", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484237786", "session_id":"443972139"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"West Chester, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.3376", "longitude":"-84.4044", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443972139"},
          { "time":"1484237707", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 8:15am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"99.233.114.242", "uid":"1262980256", "session_id":"443969848", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484237707", "session_id":"443969848"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Toronto, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"43.6605", "longitude":"-79.4633", "hostname":"rogers.com", "organization":"Rogers Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443969848"},
          { "time":"1484237502", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 8:11am", "time_total":"103", "ip_address":"99.233.114.242", "uid":"230311926", "session_id":"443963454", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484237502", "session_id":"443963454"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Toronto, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"43.6605", "longitude":"-79.4633", "hostname":"rogers.com", "organization":"Rogers Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443963454"},
          { "time":"1484237264", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 8:07am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"70.198.140.131", "uid":"212217394", "session_id":"443956396", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484237264", "session_id":"443956396"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 53.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Louisville, Kentucky, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"38.2590", "longitude":"-85.6609", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443956396"},
          { "time":"1484236699", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 7:58am", "time_total":"520", "ip_address":"72.152.35.15", "uid":"1178902880", "session_id":"443938132", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484236699", "session_id":"443938132"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Douglasville, Georgia, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.6638", "longitude":"-84.7331", "hostname":"bellsouth.net", "organization":"At&t Internet Services", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443938132"},
          { "time":"1484236698", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 7:58am", "time_total":"435", "ip_address":"174.255.203.208", "uid":"111783689", "session_id":"443938090", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484236698", "session_id":"443938090"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443938090"},
          { "time":"1484236306", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 7:51am", "time_total":"844", "ip_address":"184.7.69.218", "uid":"3280234542", "session_id":"443925116", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"6", "first_visit": {"time":"1484231536", "session_id":"443771348"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Las Vegas, Nevada, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.1810", "longitude":"-115.1701", "hostname":"centurylinkservices.net", "organization":"Centurylink", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443925116"},
          { "time":"1484235547", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 7:39am", "time_total":"307", "ip_address":"116.3.150.51", "uid":"822583773", "session_id":"443897009", "actions":"3", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484235547", "session_id":"443897009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Dalian, China", "country_code":"cn", "latitude":"38.9122", "longitude":"121.6022", "organization":"China Unicom Liaoning", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443897009"},
          { "time":"1484235366", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 7:36am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"50.92.189.230", "uid":"2974577504", "session_id":"443891345", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484161962", "session_id":"442392420"}, "landing_page":"https://corefact.customerstories.net/exit-realty/enterprise/exit-realty-grows-listings-with-corefact", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPad", "screen_resolution":"768x1024", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Vancouver, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"49.2833", "longitude":"-123.1298", "hostname":"telus.net", "organization":"Telus Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443891345"},
          { "time":"1484235172", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 7:32am", "time_total":"77", "ip_address":"70.198.205.30", "uid":"3781058220", "session_id":"443885152", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484235172", "session_id":"443885152"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 49.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.5035", "longitude":"-80.0784", "hostname":"myvzw.com", "organization":"Verizon Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443885152"},
          { "time":"1484234717", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 7:25am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"138.68.46.32", "uid":"1884424730", "session_id":"443870867", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484234717", "session_id":"443870867"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"Korean", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Santa Clara, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.3501", "longitude":"-121.9854", "organization":"Digital Ocean", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443870867"},
          { "time":"1484234604", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 7:23am", "time_total":"60", "ip_address":"158.222.151.15", "uid":"3021411460", "session_id":"443867221", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484234604", "session_id":"443867221"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"320x570", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"New York, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8116", "longitude":"-73.9530", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443867221"},
          { "time":"1484234293", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 7:18am", "time_total":"62", "ip_address":"184.7.69.218", "uid":"3280234542", "session_id":"443857620", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"6", "first_visit": {"time":"1484231536", "session_id":"443771348"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Las Vegas, Nevada, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.1810", "longitude":"-115.1701", "hostname":"centurylinkservices.net", "organization":"Centurylink", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443857620"},
          { "time":"1484234269", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 7:17am", "time_total":"30", "ip_address":"91.187.98.121", "uid":"4053066141", "session_id":"443856860", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"14", "first_visit": {"time":"1484151392", "session_id":"442121009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Albania", "country_code":"al", "latitude":"41.0000", "longitude":"20.0000", "organization":"Ipko Telecommunications Llc", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443856860"},
          { "time":"1484233636", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 7:07am", "time_total":"64", "ip_address":"74.73.236.184", "uid":"1590581538", "session_id":"443837411", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484233636", "session_id":"443837411"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Brooklyn, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6981", "longitude":"-73.9571", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443837411"},
          { "time":"1484233587", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 7:06am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.207.90", "uid":"1215294497", "session_id":"443835848", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484233587", "session_id":"443835848"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Safari 10.0 mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"375x667", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Schiller Park, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.9637", "longitude":"-87.8841", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443835848"},
          { "time":"1484233453", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 7:04am", "time_total":"120", "ip_address":"72.226.89.225", "uid":"1668037263", "session_id":"443831680", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484233453", "session_id":"443831680"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Astoria, New York, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.7611", "longitude":"-73.9319", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443831680"},
          { "time":"1484233178", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 6:59am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"107.77.216.141", "uid":"2340808964", "session_id":"443822591", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484233178", "session_id":"443822591"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 34.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x594", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"28.0222", "longitude":"-81.7329", "hostname":"att.net", "organization":"At&t Wireless", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443822591"},
          { "time":"1484233150", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 6:59am", "time_total":"518", "ip_address":"216.10.232.20", "uid":"2839882742", "session_id":"443821672", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"16", "first_visit": {"time":"1480450383", "session_id":"380216613"}, "landing_page":"https://centerforcustomerengagement.customerstories.net/summit-2016/summit/value-received-a-resource-used-continuously-for-advocacy-program-best-practices", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0", "operating_system":"Windows 10", "screen_resolution":"1366x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_url":"http://2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com/", "referrer_domain":"2017.summitoncustomerengagement.com", "referrer_type":"link", "geolocation":"Harrow, Canada", "country_code":"ca", "latitude":"42.0363", "longitude":"-82.9182", "organization":"G1 Hispeed", "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443821672"},
          { "time":"1484233034", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 6:57am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"66.87.64.218", "uid":"792721272", "session_id":"443817905", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484233034", "session_id":"443817905"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Los Angeles, California, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"34.0093", "longitude":"-118.2584", "hostname":"spcsdns.net", "organization":"Sprint Pcs", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443817905"},
          { "time":"1484233009", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 6:56am", "time_total":"219", "ip_address":"91.133.141.110", "uid":"870811435", "session_id":"443817132", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1484144517", "session_id":"441934460"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Iran", "country_code":"ir", "latitude":"35.6961", "longitude":"51.4231", "organization":"Mobinnet Wimax Expansion", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443817132"},
          { "time":"1484232919", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 6:55am", "time_total":"240", "ip_address":"100.35.183.91", "uid":"3964850921", "session_id":"443814123", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484232919", "session_id":"443814123"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"412x732", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Bayonne, New Jersey, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.6705", "longitude":"-74.1064", "hostname":"verizon.net", "organization":"Verizon Fios", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443814123"},
          { "time":"1484231812", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 6:36am", "time_total":"29", "ip_address":"166.182.81.51", "uid":"3558397162", "session_id":"443780127", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484231812", "session_id":"443780127"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Unknown mobile", "operating_system":"iPhone", "hardware":"Apple iPhone", "screen_resolution":"320x568", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"37.7510", "longitude":"-97.8220", "organization":"Wireless Data Service Provider Corporation", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443780127"},
          { "time":"1484231697", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 6:34am", "time_total":"340", "ip_address":"69.253.31.113", "uid":"2147405169", "session_id":"443776433", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484231697", "session_id":"443776433"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Wilmington, Delaware, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"39.8160", "longitude":"-75.5045", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443776433"},
          { "time":"1484231536", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 6:32am", "time_total":"439", "ip_address":"172.58.73.132", "uid":"3280234542", "session_id":"443771348", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"6", "first_visit": {"time":"1484231536", "session_id":"443771348"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Las Vegas, Nevada, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"36.0877", "longitude":"-115.1485", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443771348"},
          { "time":"1484231285", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 6:28am", "time_total":"152", "ip_address":"50.138.145.80", "uid":"1465975788", "session_id":"443763275", "actions":"2", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484231285", "session_id":"443763275"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 44.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Waterbury, Connecticut, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.5515", "longitude":"-72.9927", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443763275"},
          { "time":"1484231194", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 6:26am", "time_total":"136", "ip_address":"106.76.19.58", "uid":"1372363656", "session_id":"443760460", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1481816821", "session_id":"402115953"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/john-muir-health/varmour-protects-community-s-information-at-john-muir-health", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"India", "country_code":"in", "latitude":"13.0833", "longitude":"80.2833", "organization":"Idea Cellular", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443760460"},
          { "time":"1484231158", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 6:25am", "time_total":"241", "ip_address":"172.56.20.224", "uid":"3170774326", "session_id":"443759406", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"8", "first_visit": {"time":"1483972693", "session_id":"437978387"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 54.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"33.5207", "longitude":"-86.8025", "organization":"T-mobile Usa", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443759406"},
          { "time":"1484230647", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 6:17am", "time_total":"284", "ip_address":"172.73.87.254", "uid":"116338906", "session_id":"443742900", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"1", "first_visit": {"time":"1484230647", "session_id":"443742900"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 38.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Charlotte, North Carolina, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"35.3366", "longitude":"-80.7958", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443742900"},
          { "time":"1484230501", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 6:15am", "time_total":"240", "ip_address":"98.223.151.147", "uid":"3124504990", "session_id":"443738544", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"3", "first_visit": {"time":"1484230501", "session_id":"443738544"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Chicago, Illinois, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"41.9759", "longitude":"-87.7016", "hostname":"comcast.net", "organization":"Comcast Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"retarget"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443738544"},
          { "time":"1484229947", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 6:05am", "time_total":"218", "ip_address":"24.140.126.141", "uid":"2472576711", "session_id":"443721314", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484229947", "session_id":"443721314"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Massillon, Ohio, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"40.8182", "longitude":"-81.4918", "hostname":"sssnet.com", "organization":"Massillon Cable Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443721314"},
          { "time":"1484228523", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 5:42am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"71.90.154.168", "uid":"1828417350", "session_id":"443672341", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1483901963", "session_id":"436577374"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"1024x768", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Saginaw, Michigan, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"43.4441", "longitude":"-84.0255", "hostname":"charter.com", "organization":"Charter Communications", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443672341"},
          { "time":"1484225736", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 4:55am", "time_total":"30", "ip_address":"66.25.137.220", "uid":"2588095141", "session_id":"443594885", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"7", "first_visit": {"time":"1482975868", "session_id":"418160856"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"640x360", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"San Antonio, Texas, USA", "country_code":"us", "latitude":"29.4616", "longitude":"-98.5735", "hostname":"rr.com", "organization":"Time Warner Cable", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443594885"},
          { "time":"1484223661", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 4:21am", "time_total":"240", "ip_address":"91.187.98.121", "uid":"4053066141", "session_id":"443539140", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"14", "first_visit": {"time":"1484151392", "session_id":"442121009"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Albania", "country_code":"al", "latitude":"41.0000", "longitude":"20.0000", "organization":"Ipko Telecommunications Llc", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443539140"},
          { "time":"1484220746", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 3:32am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"91.151.147.6", "uid":"2765701572", "session_id":"443467269", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"2", "first_visit": {"time":"1484109098", "session_id":"441244054"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/retailer/top-fortune-100-retailer-solves-visibility-and-pci-challenges-with-varmour", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Germany", "country_code":"de", "latitude":"51.2993", "longitude":"9.4910", "organization":"Cetel Gmbh", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443467269"},
          { "time":"1484218453", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 2:54am", "time_total":"10", "ip_address":"95.104.74.229", "uid":"1151647893", "session_id":"443421825", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484155614", "session_id":"442228484"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Tbilisi, Georgia", "country_code":"ge", "latitude":"41.7250", "longitude":"44.7908", "hostname":"customer.co.ge", "organization":"Caucasus Online Broadband Network", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443421825"},
          { "time":"1484212223", "time_pretty":"Thu Jan 12 2017, 1:10am", "time_total":"242", "ip_address":"95.104.74.229", "uid":"1151647893", "session_id":"443310060", "actions":"1", "total_visits":"4", "first_visit": {"time":"1484155614", "session_id":"442228484"}, "landing_page":"https://varmour.customerstories.net/equens/equens-achieves-agile-security-with-varmour-and-atos", "web_browser":"Google Chrome 55.0 mobile", "operating_system":"Android", "hardware":"Other (Android)", "screen_resolution":"360x640", "javascript":"1", "language":"English", "referrer_type":"advertising", "geolocation":"Tbilisi, Georgia", "country_code":"ge", "latitude":"41.7250", "longitude":"44.7908", "hostname":"customer.co.ge", "organization":"Caucasus Online Broadband Network", "campaign": {"name":"promote", "content":"display"}, "stats_url":"http://clicky.com/stats/visitors-actions?site_id=100886848&session_id=443310060"}
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]